It's week three. It's a big finale week, and I am going to give you a week to remember.
Just you wait and see. Welcome to week three of the AI Coder course. This is going to be
really terrific, starting with a yellow day, a product day, more of Claude Code. Let's get into
it. And just to add to the sizzle, for me, just this week, the new version of Claude, Claude 4.6
Opus has come out, and also Codex 5.3. And this is old news for you. Maybe you're already on
Claude version 10 by now. But for me, it's completely new, and I absolutely love it.
I've been having a blast, and I can't wait to experience this with you this week. And wow,
do I have a week lined up for you. It's about today, looking at multi-agents, sub-agents, hooks,
swarms, lots of stuff, giving you the lay of the land with the deeper functionality you get into
with these CLI platforms. Then tomorrow, sandboxing, such a critical topic. Then looking
at the bigger picture of what it's like to work successfully with massive codebases,
because it's all very well doing these cute, simple one-person projects. But what's it like?
How are you successful when you're working with a big codebase, debugging across a large project?
And then it's all about day four. Day four is when we go crazy. Day four is when we do all
that new stuff. Swarms, and orchestrators, and all that stuff, ending with a capstone project
to remember. And if I can take you back to what I had at the beginning of last week, and from week
one, which was those eight stages of the evolution of the coding agent programmer from Steve Yegge.
And you can see that we really focused on stage five last week, as we went deep into using
Cloud Code, using the CLI, letting diffs scroll by. And we're now heading into this other, more
radical territory of stages six, seven, and eight. Multi-agents, and then many, many agents. A swarm,
and then orchestrating agents. This is the bigger deal. And it comes with a lot of excitement,
and a little bit of chaos. And I'll also remind you of the time when I explained that there are
these two different mindsets. There's the mindset you can have with a kind of mission-critical
enterprise software, where you might be micromanaging, working closely with something
like Cloud Code. You might be in the sort of mode where you are planning, and executing,
and then reviewing, and testing. And then going to the way of sort of spec-driven design with
trust but verify mindset. And this is very similar to how we were working at the end of last week,
when we were putting issues into Jira, or into GitHub, and then tracking it all the way through,
and testing the outcomes. Leaving a lot to the CLI agent, but still having a watchful eye on
what's going on. And really working with the kind of one agent, one you and Cloud Code kind of
construct. And then I went through the 2026 kind of techniques that are really surfacing, emerging
in a big way now. YOLO has been around for a while, but increasingly just going with it is
working. Ralph Loops, we experimented with them, they're really cool. And then going all the way
to this idea of like multi-agents, swarms, orchestration, that whole universe. Which is
what we will be unlocking this week. And yet again, as I remind you that you can pick the
approach that works best for your skill set, for your risk appetite, for the appetite of the team
around you, for the circumstances and type of project. But regardless of which one you choose,
always keep in mind, you're using the LLM, the coding agent as a tool to assist you to do your
work more efficiently. But ultimately, you are accountable for the code you deliver.
You're the boss, it's your work product. The coding agent is there to help you accelerate.
So this week, we're going to move fast, we're going to cover a lot of ground. And never fear,
I'm going to end the week by kind of laying out the whole ecosystem and giving you a good sense of
exactly how to approach it and when to follow which technique. But generally speaking,
the pro techniques we're going to be covering a lot this week fall into two different balancing
categories. On the one hand, there are a lot of the techniques we're going to be covered,
which give you a kind of sense of chaos in the way they magnify everything going on.
We've already met YOLO, of course, which you know what I mean now by chaos. It's like,
okay, we're just going to trust it. There's there's Ralph loops, which are definitely feel
chaotic. It's like, okay, I'm going to set it going, I'm going to go and have lunch or dinner,
or go overnight, come back and just see what's happened. And then there's this thing called GSD
that we will meet at some point. There are swarms, which is big multi agent kind of let it all
happen. All of these are different chaotic techniques. And then contrasting with that,
there is a sense of using these pro techniques to give you more control the opposite. And what
do I mean by control? You're probably wondering, what could this mean? Well, what I mean is,
for example, you can use the file system as your way of keeping everything connected and
communicating, having all of your different processes, reading and writing files that
keep track of architecture decisions, open questions, testing strategies, and use the
file system heavily as your way of coordinating across everything going on, you can have self
correcting kinds of processes. And it's sort of contrasting with Ralph loops, I guess,
rather than just having things that just keep going bigger and bigger and bigger, you can have
some of your processes responsible for testing responsible for code reviews, keeping everything
on rails, pulling everything in a kind of negative feedback, if the the chaos is a positive feedback,
and sandboxes, which we're covering tomorrow, are a way to make sure that all of the craziness
that's going on is going on in a contained world that you can always destroy and throw away and
start again. And that gives you a lot more repeatability around a process that is a bit
chaotic. And then finally, orchestration, which perhaps some insight in some people's minds
belongs more in the chaos side of it. But orchestration is about having all of your
agents out there, but having them have some kind of a hierarchy and roles and responsibilities,
such that maybe one one agent is managing others, and there's some coordination going on.
And in doing so, you're sort of reeling in a bit the craziness, and you're having things
in a more structured, organized way. So I would put orchestration firmly in the control
side of the house. And so with this in mind, with this idea that there's like there's chaos,
and there's control, my suggestion is that what you are aiming for with this, this week,
and these pro techniques, is a world with controlled chaos. That is what we're looking
to do here. Think of it like a nuclear reactor, if you remember that, when they put those rods
down to control, it's like a controlled chain reaction that's going on. And it's that mindset
that you should be having with the pro coding agent techniques. Controlled chaos. It's driven
somewhat by how mature is your project? What is your comfort zone to take risks? Where are you
at the moment, but that that would that would decide how much control and how much chaos and
how to balance the two. And I would always suggest begin with control. Don't don't start out. I mean,
you can start out with some experiments with like running a Ralph loop with many iterations
with with the kicking off a huge swarm, you can do some of these things to get some sort
of foundational ideas out there. But then when it comes to the real project, I would start with more
control and then gradually loosen your grip and allow more chaos as you see good results and then
put back more control if things start going off the rails. And so a lot of this week is about
striking that right balance that that sense of balancing the positive feedback of the chaos
that just keeps getting bigger and bigger with the negative feedback loops of the control that
reels things in and keeps things nicely on rails and and that getting that right is how you achieve
an amplification of what you're able to do and still getting good results. So with that in mind,
we're going to go through a bunch of pro features today. I will quickly explain them and then we'll
dig in and give them a try in a repo. We are going to be looking at how do you create a slash command.
We've used some some slash commands you can create your own. So I just want to show you how to do
that. We're going to look at multi-agents and sub-agents, explain the differences and use them.
Multi-agents is not necessarily a well-defined term and there's a bit of a bore of just saying
you can start up multiple cloud codes basically. Not much to it. Sub-agents is the great stuff.
That's what we'll really dig into. Agent teams is the sort of new world, the new stuff. I will
introduce it today. We won't use it until I think day four of this week or yeah yeah day four. Hooks
which is very interesting and which allows us to achieve things like Ralph loops and then just a
final topic is going to be about ways that you can create your own plugin for sharing it around
your team or even putting on your own marketplace which is a really neat pro feature as well.
So this is just equipping you with more tools in your toolkit which will then put into practice
in the coming days.