Okay, now that you know all about what we've got in store for this week,
let's look at the techniques we're learning today, and we're going to start by creating
a new slash command. How do you create slash commands for your project or for your workspace?
And it's unbelievably simple. It all comes back again to the .cloud folder. There are in fact
two ways of doing it. And the first is within .cloud, whether it's in your project
or in your home directory, applying to all of your projects. We're going to do it in a project.
You make a new folder, and you'll never guess what it's called. It's called commands. So we
made a new folder called commands. And in that folder, you put different markdown files for each
of the slash commands you want to add. So if I want to have a new slash command, I just mean I
want to be able to type slash and then type something new that is going to do something
new for anyone that's using my project. We're going to call one that is like review. We'll
call it docreview.md. It's most common to have these kinds of commands and skills and so on
be in lowercase with a hyphen. And I've actually changed them with a Cerebra skill to follow that
pattern. And we're going to do that with docreview right here. So what we put in here is what do we
want this command to actually do. So I'm going to paste in this. Review the documentation file
in the planning folder called, and then this thing, $ARGUMENTS and block caps like that.
And that just means shove in here whatever the person using Cloud Code puts
after the slash command. You'll see. Review the documentation file in the planning folder called
$ARGUMENTS and add questions, clarifications, or feedback to a new section at the end. Let's add
along with any opportunities to simplify. That's such an important thing. Let's just make that part
of what the docreview does. So we save that file. This is a file called docreview.md. And just by
virtue of saving the file inside a commands folder, we have just given ourselves a new slash
command. Don't believe me? Let's give it a try. I'm going to bring up my favorite terminal like
this. I'm going to type Claude to bring up my favorite Claude. Up it comes. Opus 4.6 is here.
Oh, my goodness. Christmas has come early. Okay. Now, a new slash command. So I can press slash.
And now I can type docreview. Look at that. Docreview is there. It is a real slash command
that we've got. And now what comes next is what we passed in as $ARGUMENTS right there. So I'm
going to type out plan.md. That's what I want it to review. Do this. Let's see what happens.
It's unraveling, apparently. I'll start by reading plan.md file to thoroughly review it.
Now let me search the existing project state to understand. It's doing stuff. It's hopefully
going to realize that absolutely nothing has happened. And now it's got a yes, empty scaffolding.
Very good. Thank you. Now let me add the review section to plan.md. So it's all doing exactly
what we wanted. It's going through and doing the analysis. And when I come back, we will look at
its results. Okay. It's completed. It's always best to close down previews that are already open
because it sometimes caches a preview. We'll open that up again. And let's go to the bottom. Let me
hide that terminal for a second and see what's going on. Document review is a new section at
the end. That seems to have worked. Our slash command has worked. But let's see what it actually
is saying. Questions and clarifications. Brand colors header is orphan. That's probably my fault.
It appears as a dangling label below the color scheme. The color scheme breaks the numbers.
Okay. Okay. We'll let it fix that. Docs versus planning inconsistency. The key boundaries.
Okay. Okay. That's my mistake. Script naming. Start windows versus start. Okay. That's another
mistake by me. That was not made by Claude.ai. That was made by me making a version of it and
then changing it. Amazing. Price history for Sparklines. That seems like a good thing.
Portfolio snapshots. What triggers recording? Chat streaming. Post response format. Quantity is real.
Is shared fractional? Yeah. No. I think shared. I think we will put here is quantity as real.
We're going to say answer. Yes. Fractional shares should be supported.
Be supported. Okay. Let's go back.
Simplification. Drop the massive API integration. Okay. Drop user ID from all tables. No. Accumulate
Spark data on the front end, not the back end. No, I don't like that much. Use a simple periodic
timer. Take a snapshot every 30 seconds. Simple. I don't like it. Simplification suggestions. I
must be honest. Simplify. Don't stream. I agree with that. I thought that's what we were doing.
That's for sure. Consider dropping the separate. Don't agree with that.
Consider dropping playwright. Don't agree with that. Okay. Let's just leave in the one
simplification. This is an example again of the human oversight. It was important that we asked
it for simplification opportunities, but I don't agree with many of them. This is where you have to
exercise some discretion, maybe ask more questions. This is where you add value and where you need to
be the boss, be the manager. We want massive API integration. That is a big part of this.
We want to have user ID on all tables so that in the future, we can be able to support multiple
users. That seems like just an oversimplification that won't help us. So does that. This seems like
a great important point. Important. Spell it right. Important. Simplify the response flow.
Don't stream. Just return. And yeah, that's exactly right. Exactly right. And all of this
is spot on. It is absolutely spot on. I'm cool. Takes one to three seconds fast enough.
Streaming is no meaningful improvement. That's a bad idea. And that's also a bad idea. So now
we've got this down to something much simpler, but I do agree with all of the points that made
in the previous section. This seems like some really, really great points. Now, it's important
to understand what this adding the slash command has done and what it has not done. What it's done
is it's given us a neat shortcut to prompting the Claude with that particular request to update the
plan document with the feedback. And that has happened. But all of that and this conversation
is part of the conversation history. If I do slash context here, we should see that we've got some
conversation history now. If I scroll up here, not much, but there's a bit. And that's what we've
just discussed. What we've not done is what sub-agents are all about. Sub-agents are when you
spawn like a separate LLM call to take care of something. Then it might add to the document and
then you come back. In which case, as far as this main chat with Claude would be concerned,
there would be no extra purple in that context. And it wouldn't know about this conversation,
but it would discover that plan.md has a new section with questions. And that's the key
distinction between using normal things like commands and skills versus using sub-agents
that will become more clear when we actually use sub-agents. But for now, this is all part of the
conversation history. So, it knows all about this. So, I'm going to say I've updated the comments
at the end of plan.md with my feedback and removed the simplifications that I disagree with.
Please now review the remaining issues and incorporate the solutions throughout plan.md
letting me know any questions.
So, this is an excellent way. This is an example of the balancing forces of using multiple Claude
codes to be iterating. But we're doing it in quite a manual way that you're already familiar
with from previous weeks. Obviously, what we're going to be heading towards this week
is increasingly automating this process of things like reviews. That's what it's going to be all
about. So, it's reading the current state of the file. We'll go through this. I don't need to hold
you up for this. You get the joke for this part. I will iterate. I will get this incorporated in
the document, answering questions sensibly. And so should you. You're going to be going through
this project too. You'll be taking it off in your own direction that might be very different to mine.
So, you should iterate through, answer questions intelligently, get the document in great shape.
And I'll see you back here in a sec. Okay, that conversation is done. The plan is updated. It
removed the last section. It also convinced me to change my mind on the front-end simplification
of one of those charts, the sparklines chart, which made a good case. It's very impressive.
I love 4.6. Opus 4.6, the new model. So, very good. Now, you may be thinking to yourself, hang on a
minute, Ed. You mentioned that there are two ways to add a slash command and we only use one of them.
So, what is the other way? Unless you've already realized the other way. You realize the other way?
Let me show you the other way. So, the other way is that skills, by default, immediately give you
another slash command. If you do a slash, you can see that of the things that appears there,
cerebras inference is one of the slash commands available to me. And that's because we have a
skill called cerebras inference that you and I wrote. And so, it's there already. So, skills
give you an instant slash command. And so, to be honest, the reality is that that's how people
do it these days. If you want, you can have commands done this way. You don't need the,
like, what they call the front matter, the YAML stuff at the top of skills because it's just a
sentence. So, this is still supported and people still use it. But most of the time, people just
focus on skills now. It's the easiest way to give yourself a new slash command. And we can equally
drag this thing over to the skills section and give it a folder of its own and make a skills.md
with a bit of YAML at the top of it. And it would all work great, too. And that is often the way
people do it. Those are the two different ways you can give yourself a new slash command. And,
of course, if it's in the .cloud directory and you check it into Git, then everyone else in
your project team gets those commands, too.