And now we get to talk about agents and sub-agents.
And let's start with agents or multi-agents.
And as I said before, I've got some boring news for you that is largely,
when people first talk about multi-agents, the simple thing they might mean
is that it's perfectly simple, of course, to start multiple Claudes.
So we've got Claude running right here and I can press this plus button.
I'm now in a new terminal and I can just type Claude and launch a second Claude.
And I can press the plus button and I can type Claude and launch a third Claude.
And now we have three different Claude prompts.
And in one of them, I could say, build the front end.
One of them I could say, build the back end.
And one of them I could say, build the tests.
And as long as I've done a good enough job of identifying the boundaries
and how they'll work together, they would probably just all work in parallel.
It's a great example of the dangers of chaos
because this plan document is not yet well enough fleshed out.
You might want to try this just as a challenge.
If you kicked off these three as three separate agents running,
I think that probably a fiasco would emerge.
I just think there's not enough substance on how they would interact
and you'd end up with bits that just wouldn't fit together.
And the agents wouldn't even know that they're each working on it.
So there would be tremendous confusion.
So there's not enough kind of fabric in place
for us to just kick off three different agents.
But it gives you a sense of what it means
and we can certainly do some small experiments in this front.
But I'm actually going to take this down a different direction,
which is totally optional.
You can do everything I'm about to do using Claude code,
but I thought I'd shake it up a bit and show you an example
of using a different coding agent as one of our other agents.
In fact, I thought I would use Codex.
And we've experienced Codex, of course, as an IDE plugin.
You can still see the Codex icon up there where it started out.
We are going to use Codex as a CLI,
the equivalent that OpenAI has to Claude code,
which is how Codex began.
So I'm going to quickly install it now
and show you how we can use it as an alternative
or really to collaborate with Claude code.
So this is the Codex CLI homepage
that you get if you just Google Codex CLI,
but I'll put it in the course resources.
And there's installation instructions.
And you can do it with NPM,
or if you're on a Mac, you can do it with Homebrew.
I'm just going to use NPM because I'm used to it.
And then you run it with just running the command Codex. That's it.
Okay, let me come back here.
I'm going to click here and run that command.
And you might have to press the plus button
if you need a new terminal outside Claude code,
because I'm not sure that Claude code
would understand that command. But here we go.
I'm installing Codex right now.
Have that installed.
And you can also use
any of the other installation techniques.
Looks like mine was already installed.
And now I'm going to run it with the command Codex.
Codex, here we go.
And I think first time it might make me log in.
It doesn't, I'm already,
so the first time it might,
it might take you through that usual
OAuth flow of signing into OpenAI,
but mine already knows I'm logged in.
I'm going to say, yes, Codex can work in this folder.
And there we go.
We are in to Codex. Very nice.
Try the new Codex app, apparently.
That's something to try,
but we're not going to try that.
I'm going to open a new screen like this.
And now check this out.
I'm going to write just a normal shell command.
I'm going to call a program that's called Codex
with the command exec.
And that is a way of just saying,
I want you to run this prompt, do it.
And that prompt is going to be,
please review the file planning slash plan.md
and write your feedback to planning slash review.md.
That is going to be my Codex exec.
And I press enter and off it goes.
This is now launching Codex as like its own thing,
running this review.
And it's going to then write the file to review.md.
And this is clearly a sense that you're getting right now
of having a different agent.
Now, it doesn't need to be Codex.
It could also be Claude that you could just run.
Of course, you can have multiple windows.
You can have Claude running twice.
But it's kind of cool that we can have
a different agent altogether.
And since I happen to have plans for both, I've got that.
And it's just written review.md.
It was very quick.
Let's open this up and review feedback planning plan.md.
And it's got all sorts of stuff in here.
It was very quick.
What's that last one I just saw?
Massive API refers to Polygon IO,
but the name is a placeholder.
That seems like a bit of a poor piece of feedback there.
This is Codex 5.3. We expect more.
So interesting stuff.
But this really gives you a sense
that we can have a powerful model like Codex
be running based on a shell command as a separate agent.
And this opens the door to lots of new possibilities
for us as we will explore.
OK, it's time for subagents.
A big topic starts now.
We've already experienced subagents a bunch of times.
First of all, just using Claude Code,
it comes with a lot of subagents built in.
There's like an explore one and a plan one.
It's something which can take on a task,
run with the task in a separate context
so that this doesn't pollute the context of the main Claude Code,
do the task, return the response,
and that goes back into the main Claude Code.
And there's like one for exploring file systems
as it builds the code base, planning one,
a bunch of others.
You see them kick off from time to time.
They sometimes print with a different color in its trace,
and you see them doing their thing,
and then they return back their information. Very common.
Sometimes they use cheaper models like Haiku
so that they're faster and cost less to carry out their tasks.
So it's great for off-boarding context,
faster, cheaper, and so on.
But context is the big one.
And also for parallelizing things
because they can run in parallel.
We've also experienced subagents
when we use some of the plugins
because plugins can come with subagent definitions built in,
and we saw that with rough loops, I think,
and with a couple of others.
So we've experienced them as we've gone along this journey.
But now we're going to build our own.
And we'll start by going back to Cloud Code.
I'm going to show you, you can type slash agents
to have a look at the different agent setups.
You can see there that first of all,
there is a create new agent option
that will guide you through the process of setting up an agent.
But again, it just turns out to be files,
and we can just create the files ourselves because we're pros.
But you can also go through the menu.
Then you'll see that there is an agent that came with a plugin,
the code simplifier agent,
because we selected that plugin at some point.
And then there's the built-in agents.
You can see here a general purpose one.
I think I mentioned the explore one that uses Haiku.
And yeah, you can see some of these built-in agents,
and you probably already experienced them running.
But we're now going to create our own.
You could do that by using this menu option,
create new agent.
We're not going to do that.
We're going to create our own by setting up the file.
And there are multiple places you can go to
to create your agents.
You can do that in the .cloud project folder,
as we will, as we've been using for commands and skills.
You can do it in your home directory .cloud
to have a sub-agent that you can use in any of your projects,
but that you won't manage in a project code base.
I don't think we'll do that, but you can.
You can actually pass them in when you start up Cloud.
You can run Cloud and then create an agent
with some flags you pass in,
which is a pretty specialized thing.
We're not going to do that.
And you can also use them as part of plugins.
If you create your own plugin,
and we probably will do that.
But for now, let's just go into Cloud,
have a new folder and call it agents.
So we now have command skills and agents,
which is where we begin.
All right, so I'm going to create a new file inside agents
and I'm going to call it,
let's just call it a reviewer, reviewer.md.
This is going to be our reviewer agent.
And now we put some stuff in here.
Okay, so here we go.
I'm going to put in,
I'm going to paste in what I just wrote.
So we're going to call this thing reviewer.
The description, carry out a comprehensive review when requested.
And now you can specify tools and a model.
The tools that it has access to
and the model that should be used,
but you don't need to.
And if you don't, then it gets access to whatever
the thing that kicks it off has.
It like inherits.
And that's what we'll do.
We're just going to keep this super simple.
You review the file plan.md
and you write your feedback to planning review.md.
This could equally be a command or a skill.
We're calling it an agent
and we'll compare the differences.
And let me delete this file here
so that that's no longer there.
It's got the answer.
Okay, that is our agent.
Okay, so I'm now going to close out of Cloud Code,
bring it back in again.
I will go slash agents to look at the agents.
And you'll see that the reviewer agent is there.
We have a reviewer agent. Cool. All right.
So you don't call an agent with a slash command.
That's not how it works.
It's not like a, sorry, like that, didn't it?
It's not like this reviewer in there.
I'm going to say, use the reviewer agent
to carry out a code, a review.
Let's just do that.
It's spelled review wrong,
but hopefully that won't cause any problems.
It should now be launching our new review agent
and be doing that. There we go.
Carry out a comprehensive review.
You can see it's the reviewer agent right there. That's cool.
It's doing its thing.
We will let it do its thing.
I will see you back here in a second.
And that completed successfully.
And it all happened.
It was written to review.md.
And as you were hopefully watching yourself,
it was the reviewer agent that carried it out.
Actually, I think that what I should have said here
is use the reviewer sub-agent.
I don't know how much that matters,
but that is the suggested way of doing it.
Actually use the word sub-agent to tell Claude
that that's what you want it to do.
But generally speaking,
one of the big distinctions
with what we were doing before,
there's a couple.
One of them is that you can't directly call it.
You have to let it decide itself
whether or not it should use the sub-agent.
And secondly, that that work that happened
to go through, analyze, think, read the file,
that all happened in a sub-agent
outside the context of the main agent,
allowing us to efficiently divvy up the task.
It allowed us to frame a prompt
for a different sub-agent
and also keep that context isolated.
Those are some of the big advantages.
And we'll go through more of them later.
And that whole file has been written here
to review.md that we can open up.
And this is a project review that's got through.
Oh, there's a critical security issue.
This often seems to happen with the sub-agents.
I think we experienced this ourselves before.
This fact that the sub-agents tend to think
that there's an issue
that .emv isn't in .gitignore,
but the key is visible in the repository.
I suppose that is a security issue in some ways,
but only with people
who have direct repository access,
which is only me.
Anyways, this happened.
We've got our review.
The sub-agent worked.
That is very interesting.
What else can we do?
You know exactly what I want to do.
I want to have Codex be the thing
that does the review.
I want to have a different AI.
Let's give that a shot in the next video.