Okay, so we'll start by deleting review.md with its silly.env worry, move that to trash,
off it goes, close down these documents, and now we will go back to our agent here and see
if we can't improve this. Okay, so I've just pasted in a new version of this called Codex
Reviewer. I've also changed the name of the files to give it nice and clean. You carry out a
comprehensive review of plan.md when requested using Codex. You are using a different AI agent
to carry out a review of the document planning plan.md. You must execute the following shell
command to carry out the review. Do not review yourself. I'm being super clear on this. All right,
with that, let's launch Claude. Okay, use your Codex-Reviewer sub-agent to carry out a review
of planning slash plan.md. That seems very clear. Let's see what happens. Let's see what happens
when we do this. It's thinking, it's celebrating, it's called the Codex Reviewer. Is it going to do
this? It's reading plan.md itself, but is it going to kick off the bash command? It's going to kick
off is run Codex. Let's see Codex exec. That seems good. Yes, we'll let it run that. Okay,
Codex is now running. So we are running a sub-agent in Claude Code, and that is launching Codex,
which is very much now being run as a sub-agent. It's really cool that we're using a different LLM
and a different LLM CLI as part of this process. Feels very sub-agenty. So that's going to happen
now. Codex is running in the background. We're going to let this complete and all of the to and
fro between the two is not going to pollute the context. And so we're going to get back in a very
efficient way, a code review that's just been written to review.md by Codex. And there we go.
We've got like a response back. It's got a ton of bits of feedback here. Let's go and have a look
at the review. It's got some strengths, that's kind of it. Some risks, gaps. It's concerned about
the skill not being defined, but it is defined. That's fine. It's because it was only looking at
that file right there. It's concerned about polygon. We're fine with this. And that doesn't
seem like a concern to me. Okay. No explicit, that's fine, I think. No authors intended, yes.
Pricing model assumptions, that seems fine. Okay. It doesn't know that
massive is the new name of polygon IO, obviously. Overall, this is a strong blueprint that should
enable parallel execution. Little does it know that it's part of the first sign of that
parallel execution. Very nice. So it's kind of cool that we've had this independent,
a different LLM go off and do this analysis, and we packaged all that into a sub-agent that ran
within Claude Code. It could have been Claude, maybe you just stuck with using Claude for the
review, and that's totally good. But that is how we are doing it. Okay. And just to make this a
little bit more interesting, I'm going to change this now, not to review planning.md, but to review
all changes since the last commit, making this a more general kind of tool. And I'm just going to
call it reviewer. And I'm going to use Codex, but you can just use Claude Code for this. You don't
need to use Codex. I kind of enjoy doing that to have this idea of a different LLM in the mix,
but it's not required. Okay. So I've updated this to be change reviewer.md, change reviewer.
And you can see it's going to carry out a comprehensive review of all the changes since
the last commit. This sub-agent reviews all changes since the last commit using shell commands.
Now, I'm saying, again, that you should do it by using a shell command to call Codex to do the work
and not review itself. But you can just tell it to do the code review itself. That will work great.
Claude Code would be good at it too. But if you also have Codex, then this is a fun way
to have different LLMs collaborate, participate in the process. So that's what I'm doing.
I am now going to come out of Claude Code. And then I am going to launch Claude again.
And now I'm going to say use, oh, I'm going to delete review.md, delete. And I can't remember
what's changed since the last commit, but I'm sure it can. Use the change reviewer sub-agent
to review changes since last commit. And we'll see what happens there. But it will hopefully go off,
make that shell command call to Codex. And we'll then have an update that will, there we go. You
can see it's on, waiting on the exec. And that will then cause a file to be written by Codex,
or in your case, perhaps by Claude, that will have that code review. And this is obviously
starting to put in place the foundations of what can become multi-agent orchestration.
And now it's completed. It did for me indeed use Codex. Maybe you've done it that way as well.
And I can see that it's got back the results of the, just looking at the changes
since the last commit, which is cool. And yeah, this is a great example of using a sub-agent
because the various to-ings and fro-ings about what actually was changed since the last commit
and deciding how it's going to look into that, and then ultimately coming up with the findings
and then writing them, none of that was put into the main context window. That was all handled by
the sub-agent. And even more for us, that was actually handled by Codex off somewhere else,
but it didn't need to be. It could have been handled by Claude Code right there. It would
still have been kept isolated from the main context, which is the whole point.
And we can see it by doing a slash context and looking at what our context window looks like.
We've got all of this stuff, but you can see there's basically no real conversation has
happened. It's all very clean because that has been taken care of by our sub-agent.
So on the list of things we were going to cover today, I had put agent teams, which is a new
experimental feature in Claude Code. And I'm going to cheat a bit in that I'm only covering
it and I'm telling you that it's to come on day four. We're going to come back to this when we
look at agent teams and a number of different constructs. But I did want to explain the
difference between agent teams and sub-agents because they are quite different. Sub-agents
really are this way to delegate one particular task to another Claude Code that's going to run
with an isolated context. And then the results will go back to the main Claude Code that called
it. And there is always this relationship that there is a main Claude Code that's just delegating
off one task that goes to a sub-agent and back comes the result. It is actually possible for
that sub-agent to have a longer term memory in those configuration settings. You can ask it to
have like project level memory. But with that caveat, aside from that, it really does feel
very much like it's just taking the one task, carrying it out. And that's its purpose in this
whole arrangement. Agent teams are a bit different. Agent teams are about assembling a whole kind of
group of Claude Codes that all run collaboratively to try and solve a problem. So it is this thing
that we're going to be covering about swarms and orchestration when you have potentially many
things all on the go at the same time. And one of the kind of big x-factor moments with agent teams
is that these different, I was about to say sub-agents but that might confuse you,
these different agents that make up the agent teams can communicate with each other. They don't
just have to go through the main Claude Code. They can also interact. You could have one agent that
is the tester that is giving test feedback directly to your front-end agent and your back-end agent.
So they all have kind of a long-running presence in your team and they are able to interact with
each other, challenge each other, try out different things, test different hypotheses,
all of those kinds of ideas. And it is experimental in Claude Code for me right
now. Maybe it's more mature by the time you see it. We will be experimenting with it,
but it's obviously a different mindset than working with sub-agents, which is
more concrete, more simple. Take a task, delegate it, get back the answer.