And last but not least,
we're going to cover creating your own plugin.
Not a common thing to want to do,
but good to know that you can, good to have seen it.
If you work in a larger team,
it can be super convenient to have a few plugins
that you've created for your team to work with,
in which case you'd be able to create them all.
You could even make your own marketplace
to be used inside your company,
and then others with Cloud Code
can add that marketplace to their marketplaces,
and then you can just pick and choose
from the plugins that are available.
It's a pro feature, it's nice to know you've got it.
Let's make a plugin right now.
Okay, and I'm going to make a,
I'm going to call it Independent Reviewer,
because it's going to, we're going to use Codex,
maybe you'll do it some other way,
but it's going to be something
that can do an independent review of changes.
And you start with a new folder,
just a node.cloud, just a new folder.
It could be in a different repo altogether,
in your own marketplace repo.
I'm going to have it right here,
and I'm going to call it Independent,
and spell it right, Independent Reviewer. Like so.
That is our new folder, which is where it all begins.
And within this, you then make a new subfolder,
a new subdirectory inside here,
which has a special name of .cloud-plugin.
That is the sort of the fixed name you have to have
for the directory, which contains some important config.
And in particular, we're going to make a file in here
that's going to be called plugin.json,
which is the sort of the manifest,
the description of what it is that we're doing here.
And you just have to know it has to be called that,
and it's, of course, in the documentation,
very clearly explained, that's what it has to look like,
and it has a particular format,
and which is the format that we will follow.
Okay, and this is the structure of it.
It is a JSON dictionary with a name,
which is Independent Reviewer, in our case, a description,
which is to carry out an independent review
of all changes since last commit,
and a version number, and that is our plugin.json file.
All right, one more thing left to do.
This top-level Independent Reviewer directory
can have four subdirectories that contain information
pertaining to this plugin,
and they are, predictably enough,
commands that can have slash commands,
then skills that can have skills,
and, of course, agents that can have subagents,
and guess what else? Yes, hooks.
So that's what we're going to create right now,
create a folder called hooks,
and this is where you can put hooks
associated with the plugin,
and within this hooks directory,
you just need a new file that is called hooks.json.
It's as simple as that.
Let's actually try that again.
Let's try that again, new file, hooks.json,
and now all I do is I go to this settings.json.
It's this exact JSON.
I'm going to cut it from there.
We don't want it in both places.
I've saved that.
I'm going to hooks.json, pasting it there.
That is putting that hook in hooks.json right there,
and so now we have our Claude plugin and our hooks. That's set.
So now we've got our independent reviewer plugin,
and we want to attach that to Claude code,
and there is a way to launch Claude
and tell it to use this plugin,
but you can only do that for one plugin at a time,
and it's not a very flexible way of doing it.
The proper way is to create a marketplace.
You can create a little marketplace just for yourself,
but then once you've pushed it to Git,
the rest of your team could use it as well.
Let me show you how you do it.
You create another folder,
which is a top-level folder for this whole repository
called .claude-plugin,
just like the .claude plugin
that was within this particular plugin itself,
and then within this, you make a new file,
and the file is called marketplace.json.
That's the name of the file that defines a marketplace,
and I'm going to paste in there some JSON
that defines my marketplace called edtools. Name is Ed.
You could call this marketplace anything you want,
but this will be mine,
and I put my name and an email,
and then a list of plugins,
and there's one called independent reviewer.
The code is at independent reviewer right there.
That's what it does,
and this defines the plugin,
the only plugin that is part of this marketplace,
but I could have many,
and this is the simple way to define a marketplace
of plugins that you will make available to others,
and once I've done that,
I can then run the slash plugin command,
and when I do that,
and let me make this a little bit bigger,
we'll have a look at how the marketplaces
are now presented to us,
so I go over to marketplaces,
and you'll see that the only marketplace
that I have access to is claude-plugins-official,
and I can go to add marketplace and press enter,
and this is where you can select
another marketplace to add in.
It could be a marketplace that you've discovered from GitHub,
it could be your company's one on GitHub,
it could be your one that you pushed to GitHub,
or you could just describe it locally right here,
which is what I'm gonna do right now.
I'm gonna do dot slash,
which means just my local directory right here,
and when I do that,
it's going to say that it knows about this.
This is now a marketplace,
and you can see independent reviewer
is the one plugin included in this marketplace.
Carry out independent review of all changes.
Exactly what we wanted.
If I go over to marketplaces right now,
you'll see that edtools is a marketplace
that's been added to my environment,
into my Claude code,
and I can have many plugins that I've added in here,
and so now I'm going to go back to discover,
or no, sorry, I'll go to marketplaces,
I'll go into edtools,
I'll say browse plugins,
here is independent reviewer
that we're looking at right now.
I can press space to say that I want to add that plugin
to my current Claude code,
and press enter,
and I'll say install for all collaborators
on this repository,
the project scope,
I'll select that,
and it's been installed.
Restart to load new plugins.
Excellent, let's do that.
I'm going to come out of Claude code,
I'm going to go back into Claude code, here we go,
and now let's do slash plugin to see what's installed,
and these are not discovered,
but go over to installed,
here we go, we've got code review,
code simplifier, context seven,
front-end design,
and up here, above all of that,
is independent reviewer.
That is installed,
which is a plugin from the edtools marketplace.
It worked, brilliant.
Now let's see if that hook is actually active.
This is so cool.
I'm going to come on in here,
I'm going to delete from here, the readme,
delete the readme,
and also move to trash,
and also let's open up the planning folder
and delete the review, move to trash,
and now I'm going to say,
please write a concise project readme.
And of course,
what we're hoping to see
is that this will kick off,
that it will write a readme,
and that is then going to trigger the plugin,
which is going to do a code review
by launching Codex behind the scenes,
and all of this is going to happen,
and we'll see now that it's still thinking,
it's still working on the main instruction.
We'll see how that goes.
Hopefully, we're going to see a readme.
We can be pretty confident about that,
but perhaps the bigger task
is whether we're then going to see the code review.
We'll say yes to this, yes.
So it's written the readme,
and now we're looking to see
if it's going to call a stop hook.
It is calling a stop hook. That's great,
and we know we deleted the stop hook
from the immediate .cloud directory,
so it's not coming from here,
from the settings.json. That is empty.
It is running the one
that comes from our marketplace,
from our plugin.
That plugin is being run,
and any second now,
we hope to see that we also have a review.md.
I will see you in a second.
Yes, indeed, we have.
Review.md has been written,
and it has noted
that there's a new hook
that is in this plugin,
and it's worried about possible recursive loop,
but I think no such risk exists,
but still, it ran.
It created review.md.
We've had success.
So look, a lot just happened,
and I understand it's a lot to take on,
and really, I want to emphasize,
if you know a lot about Cloud Code,
then this might have been quite insightful for you.
This might be stuff
you could put into practice right away,
but if you're still relatively new to Cloud Code,
then just see this as a way to get a flavor
for the kinds of functionalities that you can add.
You can make a directory that is your plugin.
Within your plugin, you have a .cloud plugin,
and this is where you put the JSON
that describes what it does.
You then have subfolders for commands,
for agents that have subagents,
for hooks, and for skills,
and that is where you configure
all of the properties of your plugin
that will be added in one shot
when someone uses your plugin,
and there is a way to just use just your one plugin
when you launch Cloud,
but the better way to do it
is to create your own marketplace,
and you do that by creating a .cloud plugin folder
and having a marketplace.json,
which is where you list all of the plugins
that are part of your marketplace,
and once you've done that,
you can simply go to the slash plugin in Cloud Code,
include this marketplace, and add on the plugins.
Those are the steps that we carried out
in order to add our own plugin right now.
Okay, look, we covered tons of ground today,
lots of different things,
and probably your head's spinning a bit
with, okay, when do I use what?
How does this all fit together? Don't worry.
As usual, we'll be going through this quite a few times,
putting them into practice,
and most of these are things that you will rarely use.
It's good to know you've got them if you need them.
Okay, just before we wrap today,
I want to just summarize the pros and cons
of subagents one more time.
So when you're thinking about using subagents
as the way to add functionality
versus things like skills and commands,
remember, first of all,
it allows you to do more in parallel at the same time.
You can have multiple subagents working together.
They can be self-corrective.
They can not only allow you to do more at once,
but they can also sort of have a negative feedback
that they keep you more under control, doing a bit less.
They can be very efficient for your context.
It's usually the first reason you use subagents
is because you pull stuff off the main context
for Claude Code,
and they can be focused on one task
that allows you to perfect the prompting,
perfect the task at hand, do one thing really well,
and be really good at it,
keeping, again, that kind of context
off your main Claude Code.
But with these strengths come a few drawbacks.
So any time you've got this kind of ability
to delegate to some other process,
you're adding more moving parts.
There's more complexity in your system,
which means that more things can go wrong
in a mysterious way that's harder to track down.
There are what I call boundary issues
or problems at the interfaces
between your subagent and your main agent
that can result in mistakes.
You can have this amplification of problems
when you divvy up the task.
Something can go a bit wrong,
and then agents go off in different directions,
and it gets more and more wrong
in a way that's kind of hard to recover,
compounding errors.
Whilst subagents are sometimes touted
as a way to save money
because you can use a cheaper model
to do some of your processing,
they can also be a way that money can add up
because you're just doing a lot more.
You've got more churn,
particularly if you've got
the sort of self-correcting agents
that are doing code reviews,
doing document reviews,
coming back for feedback.
So more is going on.
Hopefully that results in better outcomes,
but it might also mean that ultimately
you spend more getting there.
So look, needless to say,
we're going to have more time
to talk about this.
I don't want to overwhelm you
with these bits and pieces.
We'll go through some of this
in a recap tomorrow.
I also, with the plugins,
I didn't mention how you put MCP servers
in the mix as well.
So I'll touch on that,
and things called LSP as well,
which I didn't mention,
which we'll get to too.
But the main topic for tomorrow is sandboxing,
which is such an important one,
and also being able to run
Cloud Code remotely.
So a few juicy topics for tomorrow
that rounds up the couple of yellow days. And with that,
that brings us to 73% complete.
We're entering the home stretch.
Things are getting harder,
but that's because we're doing so much more,
and tomorrow's no exception.
I'll see you then.