Yesterday was a packed day when we covered tons of material.
Today we've got a fair amount, not as much, but it's really juicy stuff. I can't wait.
It's another yellow day. It's another day of digging into cloud code.
It's going to be really interesting. We're talking about the area of sandboxing,
which is very, very critical. But as part of that,
we're going to be talking about cloud execution, which is really fun.
So without further ado, let's get into it, starting with a quick recap.
So look, yesterday we covered a ton of the pro features in cloud code,
and there's a few things you might have had as a reaction to this.
One of them is a sense of being a bit overwhelmed by this.
It's so many choices, a bit similar to Andre's original tweet.
And I'm here to tell you to not worry about it.
So looking at this list, first of all, slash commands really replaced by skills
almost always now. Multi-agents and sub-agents,
the thing we're going to be focusing on is sub-agents,
and then we're going to go into teams and things,
and we'll be doing that later in the week.
So just hold that thought. We'll do a lot more of it.
Hooks, I mean, they're not used often.
They're used when you have a specific problem to solve,
and now you know how, and you can always look it up.
And creating a plugin, that's also, you know how to do it.
It might well be handy to build some plugins to share with your teams,
but most of the time you'll be building skills or maybe sub-agents
and using them yourself or sharing them in your repo
for the rest of your teammates. And that's where your focus will be.
And you already understand that.
And the good news is that the other potential objection might be
this is so Claude Code focused, and many of you, hopefully,
are also Claude Code nuts like me, but some of you might prefer Codex.
Some of you might be using OpenCode or AMP
and preferring to use one of these more open source platforms.
But particularly skills is ubiquitous. Everyone now uses skills.
And many of these other things have also taken off in a big way.
I think plugins is still, as of now, just a Claude Code thing,
but skills for sure is used everywhere.
And so these are super common.
They've become the de facto standard created by Anthropic.
So what we're learning here is applicable generally.
And if it's not already applicable to your platform of choice,
it will be probably quite soon.
And as a quick point of revision,
you'll remember that when you're creating a plugin,
you create a folder for your plugin.
And within that, you have your commands that you want to add,
your skills, your agents.
If you have sub-agents, they're in a folder called agents.
And your hooks, should you wish to use hooks.
There are a couple of other files
that you can include in there as well that I didn't mention.
And I think I alluded to the fact that I would probably mention them now.
And one of them is called .mcp.json.
And it's a JSON file that describes any MCP servers
that are included inside this plugin.
And so that's where you would put them.
And there's another one called .lsp.json.
And that's something special.
And LSP is something called a Language Server Protocol,
which is something which is able to describe to Cloud Code
the rules of a programming language,
such that it can validate that some code you've written is going to work.
And Cloud Code already knows about the common programming languages.
But if you were to work with a new programming language
that Cloud Code isn't already aware of,
then you would want to configure that as one of these files.
You would put it in a .lsp.json.
And you would put it in that plugin folder
in order for that language to be supported by that plugin.
And so that's a sort of pro feature that you may not know about.
But that's how it works.
And that's why plugins can come with the support
for additional programming languages.
And you may be thinking that's a very obscure feature
for me to be throwing in the mix.
It's pretty unlikely that most people here
are going to be wanting to use Cloud Code
for a different programming language.
The reason I mention it is because it was actually referred to
in Andre's tweet.
And I want to get to the point at the end
when you see Andre's tweet again,
and you're like, yeah, I know all of this.
So I did just want to take a moment to mention
that's where it comes from.
It's unlikely that that's something
that you would necessarily care about.
But if you do, you now know about it.
And you can just look at the documentation on the plugins
to see exactly how to add that in there,
along with the MCP servers,
along with the main four things that we just spoke about.
That's how you build a plugin.
And so now you really understand
how to configure Cloud Code with these features.
But the best way to understand it
is to actually go and try it out.
Just go through the discipline
of creating your own slash command,
creating a sub-agent like I did,
doing a hook, making a hook
just to do something useful for you.
And then even create a plugin the way I did
just to have gone through the exercise.
So you know it and understand it,
and you see where the docks are
in case you want to look up a special hook
that's going to fix a particular problem for you.
And then you've got that learning,
you've got that expertise,
and we'll put a bit of it to use later in the week.
And I'm going to throw up this page again
with the pros and cons of sub-agents,
but I think you get it.
You get a sense of when it's right to call a sub-agent.
One thing that this page doesn't talk to
is the difference between when you might use a sub-agent
versus using the kind of agent teams.
But we will get to that later in the week.
But there's this clear sense
that you can sort of delegate off to a sub-agent.
And out of all of these reasons,
the primary reason that you do it
is because you want to free up the context.
And that also is the reason
why you have some of the drawbacks as well.
They are somewhat related.
Anyways, these are the pros and cons of using sub-agents.
And that is a wrap on the topics,
the recap of yesterday.
We're moving on to today
to the very juicy topic of sandboxing.
Now your first instinct might be to think,
Ed, sandboxing doesn't sound like a very juicy topic.
It sounds like a sort of security-related,
interesting, important,
but not necessarily super exciting.
But you're wrong. You are wrong.
I will show you that this is going to be
one of the most exciting topics we've had so far
because there are two related concepts.
One concept is indeed the concept of sandboxing itself,
which is this idea
that you can sort of ring fence your resources in some way
so that they are more secure.
For example, saying,
all right, I'm going to allow Claude to change any files,
read them, write them,
do its worst, do whatever it wants,
but it needs to be within this particular subdirectory.
It can't reach outside the repo that's not permitted.
And it can use the network as much as it wants,
as long as it only goes through one of these 10 websites.
That kind of thing adds extra security to the mix.
And obviously what comes with that
is it allows you to be more productive
because you can just have a kind of YOLO level of productivity
without needing to take too much of a risk.
So it makes you more willing to be YOLO.
I think I mentioned it last week when we were YOLOing
that you might want to wait
until we've got sandboxing in place
before you do it perhaps.
And then the third thing is like a mix
of both secure and productive,
which is saying that the approval process
that you have in an unsandboxed world
where you say you press the number two to approve something
or the number one if you want to do it step by step,
it's all very well,
but there's always a risk of what they call approval fatigue
when you get so used to pressing the number one
that you're just sitting there going one, one, one, one,
and you're not actually reading it.
And so it's basically YOLOing,
but you're giving yourself a full sense of security.
And so from that point of view,
the unsandboxed approach may not be as safe as you think it is
because your brain gets tuned
to just hitting one or two all the time.
So that's probably what you knew sandboxing was,
this kind of ring fencing thing that was clear to you
and you're thinking, so what's the juicy part?
The juicy part is this blue box
that I'm about to talk about now in the next video.