Okay, the juicy part, what's coming in this blue box is what's known, it goes by lots of names,
it's confusing, it's sometimes called remote execution, it's called Claude Code on the web,
I think Codex also calls it Codex on the web, but the idea is this is about not running the
Claude Code instance on your computer, but it running somewhere else, also typically in a
sandbox, so it allows you to do more work, like to be able to kind of not delegate something to
a different agent, but delegate it to a different execution engine, delegate the work to happen
somewhere else, and it can happen in multiple places, you can have it going off and doing
10 different things remotely, it's also already sandboxed, when you do this, you do it typically
through kind of GitHub, you check everything into GitHub, you send off a task, it happens
in a sandbox world, which is why it's kind of all related to sandboxing, and it allows you also in
this crazy way to do work on the move, and when I say that, what I mean is you could be like on your
mobile phone, on your cell phone, you could be like punching an instruction to Claude, and it's going
off and doing it on the internet, in the cloud in some way, and it's coming back and telling you
something, and you're continuing your conversation, and when you get back home, you're sort of picking
up where you left off on your computer, which is crazy, but all of that is possible, and that's what
I mean by juicy, it really is, it's really cool, and it's worth mentioning that this is a hugely
evolving space, there are multiple different kinds of offerings and flavors, and so it's somewhat
confusing, I will try and keep the course resources up to date, you may have different set of offerings
than I have, and that's one of the challenges of being in this space that's moving so fast,
but I'll do my best to take you through the latest stuff that's there, it's also, Claude
Code was the first to do this, I think, but Codex now offers all of this too, I think some of
the others do, and if they don't for me, they probably will for you, so you'll see that
there's kind of analogous offerings from the different people, and you can pick the one
that works for you, but the general principles is what I'll go through, and I'll give you as before
the example specifically for Claude Code, but you can probably apply this to whichever platform
that you're most comfortable with. Okay, so with this, I'm going to talk you through three
different approaches, three different things we're going to do that some blend of those two techniques,
and that is what we will then go and do, and it's a bit confusing, as I say, because there are so
many different ways to slice this, but I just want you to be crystal clear on these three different
ways, and I'm going to start by saying what's one of the things that we're not going to do, I'm not
going to show you what would be the kind of original way this used to be done, which is using
Docker, or for people familiar with VS Code, it's what they call dev containers, dot dev containers,
which is a way that you can use Docker, which itself gives you this box within a box, remember
that's how I explained it two weeks ago, and some of you probably know Docker very well, it gives you
an environment in which to do it, that's a kind of simplistic way of doing this, everything we're
going to do is sort of saying, okay, yeah, that's a given that you could do that, but we can do
something better that's more powerful in some way, so you've always got Docker and dev
containers if you want it, but this is all taking it a step further. Okay, approach one is something
that maybe you'd call a native sandbox, just sandboxing, this is functionality that is built
into Claude Code, I don't think as of now that Codex is yet doing this, or Gemini CLI,
but I might be wrong, and even if they're not now, they might well be by the time you're seeing this,
but this is built into Claude Code, it's triggered by doing a command slash sandbox, and then you can
set up Claude Code so that it runs in a sandbox, meaning that things get auto approved within that
sandbox, I'm pretty sure, yeah, yeah, Cursor has this functionality, right, we saw it ourselves,
they have like a built-in sandbox, auto approves a bunch of things within their sandbox,
so Cursor through the user interface has this, Claude Code has this sandbox built-in,
and this is something that's like, it's as if you're running your own Docker, but it's more
efficient than that, it's better than that, it has lots of characteristics that make it very desirable
as we will see, and of course it's running on your machine, so we're not doing anything remote
at this point, it's local, and the main way that it's better than running a Docker container is
just that it's much more lightweight, it's implemented at the OS level, so it's very easy
and quick and lightweight, and runs well, there is a catch though, there's a catch which you're
not gonna like, the catch is that if you're a Mac person like me, this is super easy,
if you're on a Windows PC, then to use this, at least as of now, you have to be set up to use
something called WSL, and if you already know about WSL, and maybe you already use WSL,
then that's all good, you know exactly what you're doing, if you don't know it, and it's about
running a Linux machine on your PC, and developing within that Linux machine, it's not worth you
taking that on right now, so you should focus on the other two approaches, if you're not familiar
with WSL, but if you are, then you can use it with that, and if you have a Mac, then you're
in great shape, and Linux is also great shape, okay, so that's the first approach, the second
approach is the absolutely crazy one, this is, it goes by lots of names, the product name is
Claude Code on the Web, and Codex calls it Codex on the Web, so this on the web is obviously like
a thing, perhaps the technical way of describing it would be like a managed cloud sandbox, it's
managed in that Anthropic are taking care of it, they're running Claude Code for you, and it's a
cloud sandbox, it's on the cloud, and it's in a sandbox, so that's what this is, it's basically
you're connecting with Claude Code from your CLI on your computer, but when you run
something, it's not running on your computer, it's contacting Anthropic, they're spinning up Claude
Code remotely on like their boxes, and running it there in a sandbox, and that sounds like a whole
lot of plumbing and configuration, and crazily, you can do it just by putting a little ampersand
at the beginning of your Claude Code instruction, and then just typing out anything that you
would have said to Claude Code, and it doesn't happen on your box, it happens out on the cloud,
and that sounds too good to be true, but we'll see it, you can also make a command, and not
within Claude Code, but just on your normal PowerShell, of instead of Claude, you type Claude
remote, and then your command, and the same thing happens, and off it goes, it's crazy, so
that's one thing, and then there's another thing you do, which is also crazy, which is you
can go to your GitHub repo, and you could raise like a GitHub issue, and tag it to Claude, you put
at Claude, you like address it to Claude, and insanely, Anthropic will spin up a Claude Code
in the cloud, connect to your GitHub repo, do the work, and then say when it's done, it's like what,
that really happens, as we will see, and this needs you to install a GitHub app called the
Claude GitHub app that we will do, it's tightly linked to GitHub, so you do need to have all of
your code checked in, everything is organized by the Claude Code on the web, we'll clone the repo,
pull down the code, and operate on it that way, so everything has to be checked in, and then
there's the one more feature that is like what, the other feature is called Teleport, and Teleport
allows you to sort of grab one of the Claude Code things that's running out there, and have
that become your active session, it's like you're jumping into it, it sounds very sci-fi,
and it takes a while to get familiar with this idea, but it's really cool, and slash tasks
is a way of just seeing all the different tasks that are running, so one way to think about this,
I was saying yesterday that of course a simple way to have multiple agents working on your work
is just to press that plus button, and run lots of Claude CLIs, this is effectively doing that,
except the Claude CLIs are not running on your computer, they're running on Anthropic's computers
instead, but otherwise it's quite similar, and you can sort of attach to any of those conversations,
so that's how it works, it sort of has to be seen to be believed, which is what we will do
in a minute, and then the final one is really interesting, and this is a new emerging idea,
which is, I'm calling it third-party Claude sandbox, I don't know to what extent that is
like the most official way of calling it, but I think that's probably the most accurate,
this is when you're not using Anthropic, but you're using another company who has an offering
that allows you to run something like a container in the cloud that is sandboxed,
and usually in this case is designed for coding agents, so it's sort of optimized for that use case,
and one that's recently for me has really taken off is called Sprites.dev, made by the people
at Fly.io that is a really great hosting platform, and this is particularly notable because it's very
fast, very simple, very flexible, and it's designed for a few things, but one of them is
very much like a Claude code on the web in a managed sandbox, so it's really, really convenient
for that use case, and one of the other points to make about this is that this one is of course
applicable to any coding agent, so this is something that you can use no matter what you've
chosen as your coding agent of choice. All right, so these are the three, it is a bit confusing,
but I think it's going to become much more clear when we actually put them to the test,
when we try them out, and of course that's what we're going to do right now.