Okay, here I am back in VS Code, back in Claude Code.
I've also, as it happens, I've uninstalled that plugin
and deleted those files and pushed to Git.
The only thing I've now got set up in my .claude,
everything is empty except the Cerebra skill.
I'm keeping that around
because we will need that at some point.
Okay, so here we are in Claude Code
and I'm gonna type slash sandbox.
There we go, sandbox disabled, it says.
Sandbox, press enter to configure.
Okay, so we're now gonna set it up.
Now, it is clever in that it knows
what needs to be installed and it should guide you
through the installation process.
If anything, if it doesn't give you
all of the steps required, I will, of course,
have links in the resources to what you need to do.
And you can see that there's a few different options.
The current thing is no sandbox.
There's a sandbox, number two would be to give me a sandbox
which allows a bash, shell scripts to be run,
and regular permissions.
But number one is like a sandboxed version of YOLO.
Commands will try to run in the sandbox automatically
and attempts to run outside
fall back to regular permissions.
Explicit ask-deny rules always respected.
So you can always add a deny rule
if you don't want it to do something
and it has a link to the docs in there as well.
So I'm gonna go with that.
I'm just gonna show you on the overrides,
you'd be able to set up overrides, but let me press one.
Let's go back there now to sandbox and have a look at here.
This is now the current setting.
Overrides is where you can choose to have a fallback
that would be then no longer in the sandbox
or have it be strict.
And then config is where you can set things
that are allowed and denied.
And you can see a few things in there
that look like they probably should be denied,
which is just as well.
Okay, so the sandbox mode is now on
and that should mean that we are in good shape
to be running things with fewer need to approve permissions.
Okay, so I'm going to run something
which is gonna require it to a few things.
And I should probably point out the,
I think what it can do within the sandbox
is run bash scripts, shell scripts,
and it can read and write files to its heart's content
without asking me anything.
Web searches, it will still ask me,
but once I've approved that,
then it should be good to do it.
So it does need to do that still.
But I'm gonna say,
please carry out comprehensive research
and write three documents to the planning directory.
And I'm asking it to research the market data API
from Massive, formerly Polygon,
write a document about that.
Research how or think about how we would like
to build our interface, our market data interface,
write a document about that.
And finally research how we would do
a market data simulator
and write a document about that too.
So I'm setting all of that off.
It's running now in our sandbox mode.
That means it should only be asking me
for permissions to do web searches.
Everything else that it might need to do,
it should just be able to go off and do the task.
No need to ask me for anything.
And we will see what happens.
It's doing its thing.
It's garnishing.
It's doing tasks.
It's researching. It's thinking.
It's reading files.
A lot going on without it needing to ask me for stuff.
So I will see what's happening.
And now here we go.
Oh, it does want, so I see, I see.
So to use this plugin,
this isn't something that I've given it permission for
before and it's asking to use the context seven plugin
that I quite forgot that I had.
But of course that is a wonderful way
that is much better than doing the research
from a web search.
And that's using an agent.
So that's going off
and it's now using the other, the query docs command.
So we'll let it do that too.
And those are all happening
and it's now going to be creating this documentation.
And I will see you in a minute when all of this finishes.
Okay, and that's done.
And there are the documents and it all looks pretty good.
I haven't reviewed them because I'm not going to
because we're going to just let this thing keep going.
We're going to be much more trusting this week.
The couple of things to bear in mind,
if you look through the documents,
if you do want to use this strategy for sandboxing,
it is worth reading the docs.
It goes into more detail about how you can configure it
in a more granular way, for example,
to allow web searches to various places.
It also has some very important security concerns
that you do need to keep in mind if you use this a lot
and it's laid out very nicely in the docs.
It also does mention,
I noticed that support for native support for Windows
not having to go through WSL is coming soon.
So maybe by the time you see this,
it already supports Windows out of the box.
But that is the first type of sandboxing.
This is the one that's built into Cloud Code,
super simple and very convenient,
just slash sandbox to get it running.
Okay, and now we're going to progress
to the remote Cloud Code on the web.
Okay, I'm really looking forward to this.
The first step, there's a bit of a setup thing,
just a little tiny bit of setup.
The first step is to bring up a browser
and go to claude.ai slash code,
claude.ai slash code.
And it takes you over to this screen here,
code with Claude anywhere, as you will see.
Run multiple coding tasks in the Cloud seamlessly
between your browser, terminal or mobile, mobile.
And the first thing you need to do,
the reason we've come here is you need to connect
Claude with your GitHub account.
So you press connect to GitHub,
and it's now going to want to authorize Claude.
And it's going to hopefully connect my GitHub to Claude.
There we go, something is happening.
Connect your repos, install the Claude Code GitHub app
in your repositories, connect them to Claude.
You can manage this later.
So we might as well do it right now.
So when you've got this screen here,
you then press connect repositories.
This is going to bring up this,
and I'm going to go into installing Claude into repos.
And I guess what I'll do now is I'll click
on only selected repositories,
and I'm just going to pick this one for now
and press install and authorize.
Depending on your comfort,
you can do it to all repositories or whatever you would like.
Okay, there's just a small little bit of extra setup
still needs to be done.
I'm going to go into Claude again.
There's a command you need to run
to set up something called the Claude app
in the GitHub repo.
And when you do that, it's going to complain
if you don't have a few things
already installed on your machine.
The way you do that is I do slash
and then I start typing install.
You'll see that install GitHub app is one of the commands.
If I run it, it's going to complain
that there's a few things not installed.
The GitHub CLI, being able to run the command gh.
And conveniently, it tells me exactly where I go
to find out more about how to do that.
And it tells me the commands to run on a Mac
and the commands to run on Windows
and the command for Linux or where to go for Linux.
So that's very convenient.
I'm going to run this one because I'm on a Mac.
You're going to run that one if you're on a Windows PC
or if you're on a Mac like me, you're going to run this.
And then after that, I'm going to run gh auth login
to log in from this computer.
So I'm going to do that right now.
So I'm going to come out of Cloud Code, escape from that.
And command C, there we go, I'm out.
I thought I was stuck in Cloud Code for a minute.
And now I'm going to run that brew install command.
I'm going to come in and do that.
And then after that, I'm going to do the gh auth login.
And then there we go, it's happening already.
And once I've done that, gh auth login,
which will take me on the GitHub auth flow.
And then I'll come back in a second once I'm logged in,
and then we should be ready to go.
And it took me through some shenanigans
where it launched a web browser as these things often do,
and I had to log into GitHub.
And meanwhile, it printed a code in the PowerShell
in this terminal, and I had to type that code
into the screen, and then we're all set.
And now I am auth, I'm logged in
to the GitHub command line interface from my computer.
I should also mention, by the way,
that I've done a git add dot and a git commit,
so that if I do a git status,
we can see that everything is up to date and done.
All right, and now I'm going back into Cloud again.
Now look, we're almost done with the shenanigans,
but there's just potentially a little bit more to be done.
And this depends a bit on how you've gone
through the flow so far,
and also, Cloud Anthropic is changing this
from time to time, so always look out
for the course resources for the latest.
But come back in, now I've actually gone
to a new blank project,
just so you see what it's like first time.
And one more time, now that we've got everything installed,
I'm going to do this slash install GitHub app,
and I'm going to select this repository,
which for you is going to be the finally repository.
And I'm coming in here, let me bring up this browser
so you can see, and we are now going to say
that we want to install the GitHub app in this repo
that you may have already done,
but you may get to see this screen.
And when you press that configure button,
you come through to here,
which is a screen you might've seen from earlier,
so this might not be necessary.
You might need to make sure
that you select this repository, I've just done that,
or you can choose all repositories,
and then press save,
and it takes you back into the Cloud screen.
You then have to go back to Cloud Code,
which is sitting here and says,
press enter once you've installed the app,
and you press enter.
And look at what comes up here.
It says, select the GitHub workflows to install.
This is a key step.
This is where you are installing a couple of workflows
into your GitHub repo, which is going to control Claude.
And it's going to allow you to do things
that have a GitHub issue,
tag Claude, and Claude will take it over.
If you see what I mean.
And you will, once you've made sure
that these two are ticked,
you can press the space bar to untick,
the space bar to tick.
Now they're both ticked.
You hit enter, and you can then say
that you want to have a long-lived token
that comes with your Claude subscription.
And then at that point,
you press enter one more time here. So here we go.
I'm going to press enter here,
and off we go back in here.
Claude Code would like to connect
to your Claude chat account.
You press authorize.
And now that has been done.
And now you come back here one more time,
and it will automatically open up GitHub.
And what you're looking at here,
and this takes a while to get our head around.
You're looking at a pull request in the repo.
For you, this will be in the repo we're working on,
finally, but I've already done it.
So I'm doing it again with something called Test Flow.
But it's created a pull request
that is to add a GitHub workflow into your repo.
I will try and put some notes down on this,
or ask me in Udemy Q&A if you're confused.
And you simply have to press the create pull request here to create.
This is a pull request.
And then you need to press the merge pull request.
And it says add Claude Code GitHub workflow.
Confirm the merge. That is done.
And that might have seemed all quite mysterious to you,
but what you've just done is you've followed a process
which has added a special workflow into this GitHub repo,
which is going to allow Claude to access it.
You've really bridged Claude with your GitHub repo.
And ultimately, the effect of all of this
is that if we're in the finally repo, looking at it here,
you'll see that there is this folder .github slash workflows.
And if I come into that,
you'll see that there are some YAML files in here,
claude-code-review and claude.yaml.
And these are new workflows added to our GitHub repo
coming from Claude.
And that means the setup is complete.
So the bottom line is that all of this
is about within Claude Code,
running that slash command, install GitHub app,
and then just following the instructions,
dealing with pasting tokens from one place to another,
following all of the commands
and making sure that everything is followed.
And you can see it's telling you right here
the steps that you need to do in order to complete this
and then any key to exit.
And finally, we're done with setup.
It's time to put this to work.