So the result of all of these shenanigans is that we are now able to use Claude Code either here
locally on my computer as always or remotely have Claude Code work for us in the cloud.
And there are five different ways that you can do it and they all have, well not all of them,
some of them have some differences and I'm going to quickly go through all five of them
and experiment with some of them. And I say some of them because AmpliPix having some production
outages at the moment which slightly limits what I can do but it doesn't matter because the ones
that I can do right now are still some of the coolest. So the simplest thing you can do is that
if you have any command you've got like hey what's two plus two, which no doubt Claude Code will not
have much of a problem with, it's thinking about that four, you can put an ampersand before it
and then that same thing will not run on your computer but it will spawn AmpliPix in the cloud
and run it and get you back the answer. But that's the thing that has a production problem right now
that means that it's not going to work for me and a subset of users and not clear quite which subset
it's not able to do it right now which is too bad and running slash login doesn't
do anything. But it will work for you and more than that you could put in any instruction you
want you can put in and redo my readme and write me a new document whatever you want you can put
it in there and it will go off and do it and you should experiment. And once you've done that you
can do slash tasks and you'll see a list of what else is running out there and that's pretty cool
and yeah this these are all unfortunately I've got I've got nothing there but you will have things
if you've just kicked something off and you can kick multiple things off and have them all
off and running as different tasks at the same time just as you could press plus and have lots
of them running on your own box but but it doesn't need to be on your box it can be out there on the
cloud running in a little sandbox environment and when it completes you get back the results and I
should mention that that the work that's happening on the on the cloud when you kick it off the full
context of the conversation so far is sent off to the cloud so it can continue at work it's already
been doing up to that point and that's pretty cool okay so that's the first way to do it the
second way is that you can also just call from the command line I've got add a claw code you
can just say clawed dash dash remote and then just put a command in here like uh again what is two
plus two but or something more meaningful now this is also not working at the moment for me
but it will work for you you should try it you'll see it's great uh and for me I'm gonna get an
error message there we go unable to create remote session thank you anthropic but it's been that way
for for a couple of days but uh I'm sure it'll be fixed very soon it'll certainly be fixed by the
time you see this and so you should try it and see it but luckily for us there are another three ways
to do it that all have some differences and other ways that I would typically do it and that's what
we're going to do next let's go for for number three and number three is to go to claude.ai
code which comes up with this kind of interface and the first time you come into this if you this
should have happened in the previous flow when we first came into it that they call the onboarding
you may have needed to set up an environment and the first time it does it so this comes up like
this and it asks you whether you the network access it does it actually with like three big
buttons on the screen do you want none trusted or full and trusted is the usual one to pick there
and this is known as your cloud environment and you can think of it as a setup of the thing
out there on the cloud that is able to run things remotely and what you can then do is pick a repo
which which uh you can see I've been playing around with this but finally is the name of our
repo and then finally you can give a command and that command will then run on the cloud this is
a web browser this is a little claude code thing if I say what is two plus two which is again not
the best use of opus 4.6 and you can see it calls the session basic arithmetic expression
starting claude code all this thing is happening somewhere this this this machinery is spinning up
trillions of floating point calculations are happening in order to calculate two plus two
and it does indeed get the right answer and we could continue the conversation there
or we could put a fresh chat message right here okay so let's put this to actual work
I'm saying please read all the documents in the planning directory then design the market data
back end in detail write a new document called market data design that has code snippets and
examples to implement all the market data functionality that's a good task let's assign it
so we're doing this in a web browser so off on the cloud it's launched a new session that's
happening right now claude code is spinning up in an isolated environment it's reading all the
documents and this is all happening my machine is idle nothing's happening on my machine I know you
get it uh so it's all running and uh I'm gonna let it do its thing and and then I'm gonna hope
to see that in github there's going to be a new file created for the design of our market data
I'll see you in a sec so one thing I'll say is that claude code on the web is a bit slower a
tad slower than running it locally this just took 10 minutes to write a document and it's also a
little bit flaky it's called a research preview you can see it says there maybe by the time you
see it it's going to be a bit more stable but I had to ask it twice because one of the times it
just seemed to sort of stop and be like all right that's it I'm out peace out but uh asking it again
and and then just being a bit insistent and waiting and being patient and it has now done
something and it's written 1490 lines and if I flip over to the github repo you'll see at the top
here that there is indeed uh something that's been pushed that's waiting for a pull request
so we can see what it's done and choose whether or not to accept it in github and so we'll do
that I'll press this compare and pull request button up it comes it says comprehensive
implementation update for the market data subsystem and here it is it's made a file
called market data design it's put it in the planning folder and it's a big old document
with lots of stuff about how it should work and some code snippets and other things this all looks
like it's been very thoughtful uh I'm going to take its word for it I'm going to think that that's
a nice bit of planning that's been done we will go ahead we'll press the create pull request button
so that we do this then we are going to merge in this request confirm the merge and that is now
going to be part of the main branch so that if it says merged up here if I go back to the code
and if I go into planning we will see that uh hopefully yes market data design.md is a new
document in here and this document was written in its entirety by Claude Code here it is with
a table of contents with Claude Code running on the web so to recap I've shown you three ways to
run Claude Code remotely using the ampersand uh in just in a Claude Code session running locally
using Claude dash dash remote from your computer from a terminal the third way is by going to
claude.ai code and then using Claude Code on the web just in a browser which is kind of cool and
now for the fourth way the fourth way is if you have the Claude mobile app on your phone you open
it up the main navigation has a has a it says chats projects artifacts and then it says code
and if you tap there then it will come up with a list of the sessions the same sessions that you
had listed out just there on the screen a moment ago and there's a black button that says new
session and you can press that and it's exactly the same interface that we were just looking at
and basically we can do exactly what we just did from your phone you can give it an instruction
I want you to write this document I want you to build this feature I want you to do this
and then submit it and then when you come back there will be something ready for you to build a
pull request and merge in your github repo and you can drive it all from your phone and you can have
many sessions running you can kick off multiple of these from your phone and I don't know why that
feels so cool why that's so much better than just being able to go to a web browser and do it but
somehow it does and you should do it just so that you've had that experience of bringing it up and
you should pick some moment to do it like when you're out at dinner somewhere or something and
you just sort of casually drop in oh I'm just going to my team work on a few a few bits of
few features that they're going to build for me just a second and then I'll check it out over
over dessert so yeah you should do that that is the fourth way to drive claude code remotely and
now a drum roll please for the finale for the fifth way to run claude code on the web I bring
you to github right here we are in github we are looking at the finally repo here it is and I want
you to flip over to issues now we're in a github issue no issues it's a nice state to be but we're
going to make one press new issue to come up with a new issue and the name of the issue is going to
be build complete market data back end that's going to be what we're about to do okay let me
paste in all my instructions I want you to read all the documents in the planning directory then
build the complete market data back end including an interface to a provider of market data a
unified market data interface and a market data simulator all of that with full unit tests that's
what this issue is about and I'm going to add the the immortal tagging at claude and with that
simple instruction I am I am saying that I want claude to do this work for me that's it and now
with that I'm just going to press the create button so that is something which I have I have
messaged I have I've tagged it as being at claude that's how I want this to happen and what we are
hoping is that this issue is going to be one which is going to be sent to anthropic to our claude in
the cloud to take care of this on our behalf and just a few seconds later this appears suddenly
out of nowhere I did nothing I just pressed enter suddenly claude bot now claude code is
working I'll analyze this and get back to you view job run and so with that just by virtue of tagging
it with claude we have launched a claude uh instance that's running doing stuff there's
its to-do list it appears again I didn't touch it I promise it appears there all within this
github ui it's off and running just because we tagged it in an issue and this makes all of those
shenanigans a few minutes ago worthwhile right this is really cool so you can now just create
issues in your repo tag claude and have something spin up in the cloud and have it run for you on
this and look at that it's read all the planning documents that got ticked off again this time you
saw my hands were up here I was gesturing you knew that I didn't do anything uh so obviously this is
going to take a while the fact that it took 10 minutes to write the documents means that it could
be off off taking a long time over this but but just think about how you could set up a ton of
different issues a bit like we set up jira tickets last week and you could have lots of claude
claude code instances working on them in parallel and that's cool