Well, look, I'm honestly shocked, but it only took seven minutes or something,
and six minutes less than this, and less time than it took to write that document.
And it went through all of those to-dos,
and it then gave me this beautiful output explaining what it's done
with the testing, with all of the things.
There's all of the tasks that it completed.
And it says it's made 90-plus comprehensive tests,
which sounds amazing.
So with all of that, it's then made a PR that we can then go in.
Oh, it's made this branch that we can then make a PR
and then merge in the changes and see what we think. Let's do that.
So I go in, I press Create PR. Up it comes.
We can come down and have a look at all the things that it's built here.
It's changed 21 files with 1,600 lines of code in here.
You can see some of this stuff.
This looks, well, I don't have time to go through this carefully,
but I'm pleased to see that there's plenty of what appears to be not unwieldy.
There's some initial setup, not unwieldy functions here.
Okay, well, we'll just go with that.
We're going to say Create Pull Request.
We're going to do a merge.
It should be fine.
Merge Pull Request, Confirm Merge.
And that is done. How about that?
And now, of course, you could just go in and make a ton more issues,
make an issue to go and carry out the tests, to do a code review.
You could be just throwing in lots and lots of issues to get your project done.
But we have other things to try.
So just in case you're getting disorientated by how much we're covering today,
I just want to remind you of the three techniques we're going to be doing.
And we've done the blue and the purple, and we're about to do the yellow.
The blue, we used native sandboxing, slash sandbox,
so that we could control the environment we're running in
and auto-approve a ton of stuff.
That was the blue.
And then we did the purple.
And the purple, within the purple,
there are five different ways to run Claude code in a sandbox out on the web.
A couple of them didn't work for me because Anthropics having production problems,
but the mobile one was really cool.
And the GitHub one was absolutely fantastic.
I hope you like that.
That is such a way to work.
Imagine combining that with the techniques we learned last week,
how you could just be firing off GitHub issues and just letting it run in the cloud. Okay.
And now finally, the yellow, the third approach,
which is to use a third-party cloud sandbox.
And I suggest this is optional for you
because this is something which you may be very satisfied
with what we've already covered,
very happy with Anthropics Cloud if you want to use any cloud
and not need to use a third-party cloud sandbox.
It's more, particularly if you're not using Claude, say,
this is something which is useful to know that these things exist.
They are a new up-and-coming thing.
And in particular, I'm going to pick one which has got a lot of press recently,
made by fly.io, but there are a bunch of them.
And you could pick whichever one you like.
I'll give you this example.
We're going to set up an account.
The product is called Sprites.dev.
And it's this idea of having a really simple, nice sandbox in the cloud.
We'll set one up, we'll use it, and then we will move on.
We won't dwell on it too much. Let's go do that.
So this is what you get if you go to Sprites.dev in your favorite browser.
You get a nice little website,
stateful sandbox environments with checkpoint and restore.
So they give you this sort of isolated world where you can operate in,
but they add in some extra features to make it super useful,
like being able to go back in time.
It's a hardware-isolated execution environment for arbitrary code,
a persistent Linux computer.
Whether it's an AI agent, like Cloud Code,
or a binary your user just uploaded,
Sprites are the simplest answer for where should I run a blob of code?
And look at that, right now they're offering $30 of trial credits.
Maybe you have something similar.
It says, create like 500 Sprites for free.
That sounds good.
So I'm going to sign up now and go through a quick sign-up flow.
It's completely up to you.
You may have had your fill of remote execution,
but should you wish to, then go through it with me
and I'll see you back in a sec.
And after signing up, it is telling me it needs my credit card,
which I know for some of you is like, uh-uh.
So even despite the free credits,
it's going to want me to put in a card, which I will do now.
But as I say, you can choose to just watch me go through it
and consider it for the future if you'd prefer.
Now, after I put in my credit card,
it then slightly confusingly bounced me to fly.io's landing page
because Sprites.dev is built by fly.io.
And I had to just know to get back to Sprites.dev
and then I was then logged in.
And the first screen it shows you
has the instruction that you use
to install the Sprite command line interface,
the Sprite command.
And that instruction contains within it your key.
And so I can't show it to you because it has my key
and you'd be able to mimic me, which would be no good.
But you have to take that exactly as it says,
paste it into any terminal,
and this one will do just fine,
the one we've already got for finally,
which I have right here in VS Code,
and put it in there and it will work
and then Sprite will be there.
And once you've done that, you type Sprite login
and it will then pop up a browser window
and you sign in with the same credentials you just used
to make sure that you're then fully signed in.
And I, of course, have already done that.
So now I am signed in and I can use the command Sprite.
And you will not believe how easy it now is. Here we go.
Hold on to your heart.
You're not gonna believe this.
I'm gonna type Sprite.
And then the command is Sprite create.
And that means I want to build an instance,
an engine up on the cloud that I can just use myself.
And you give it a name.
So we'll call it like, I don't know,
like Remote Worker.
We'll call it Finally Worker.
So it's clearly something that we're building for us. Finally Worker.
It's gonna be our worker.
Created Finally Worker in 0.6 seconds.
Fly.io take great pains to tell you how proud they are
of how fast it is to spin up your own box,
which in the past has been something
that has been problematic.
Kind of getting access and installing everything
on a server in the cloud.
And for them it is, bam, it's ready for you. So it is there.
And we've created it and we can now use it.
And this prompt, Sprite at Sprite,
is telling us that we are here connected
to something that is remote.
We're connected to this box out on the cloud.
Okay, so if I run the command ls
to see what is in this directory
that we are sitting in on the cloud,
there's nothing there at all.
Well, let's change that.
Let's do git clone and then paste in our repo,
our finally repo, and bam, now do an ls.
This finally is there on this box in the cloud.
CD finally, let's look at it.
It's everything's there.
A backend, cloud.md, a license,
the planning directory, and a readme.
Okay, well, that's something.
We've got our repo here.
What should we do next?
Well, I've got an idea of what we should do next.
We should run Claude.
We should just type Claude. And guess what?
It comes pre-installed on all of the boxes.
So when you run Claude, up comes Claude code.
And it says, choose the style that works
and the usual questions that you may remember
from the first time you ever launched Claude code.
We'll say that we want dark mode.
And then it's going to want us to log in.
And this is confusing
because it's going to want to do this Claude account login,
but this is all running out there on the cloud.
So it's going to try and like, you know,
log in, bring up a browser window
on some remote box in the cloud.
But no, they've thought of all of this.
They've got it all worked out
so that when I press one here,
it launches the browser locally on my computer.
I press authorize and then I go back here again
and I've logged in to Claude on this remote box.
Press enter to continue.
Warning, Claude code running in bypass permissions mode. Yes, I accept.
They have automatically configured Claude
to be in dangerously skip permissions in YOLO mode.
And that's okay because it's running
on this isolated hardware out there on the cloud.
It doesn't matter what it does.
Nothing can happen.
It's just running with a public repo out on the cloud
and bypass permissions is on.
And this is a classic example of what it's like
to run on a server in the cloud in a total sandbox,
on a third party sandbox.
And as a particular pro point,
you might've noticed that it's running
an older version of Claude code
and it's using Opus 4.5 and I want to be on Opus 4.6.
And that's only because it's like a fresh install on this box.
If I get out of Claude code
and then I launch Claude code again,
it automatically updates itself
and we are now on the latest version and on Opus 4.6.
And here we are running a version of Claude code.
It feels like it's just running on my box, right?
It looks like, but especially as I'm using the terminal
inside VS code in the finally repo,
it feels just like it's running here, but it's not.
This is running out there on the cloud
in a third party sandbox.
And so let's give it a command. Here we go.
Please read all the documentation in the planning folder.
The market data backend has been implemented with tests,
carry out a comprehensive code review, run all the tests,
write your conclusions to market data review
in the planning folder.
And we can set this off.
It's running out there on the cloud, not on my computer
in this third way, this different way of doing it
using a third party sandbox instance.
And this is really cool.
And this is very much, this is the latest.
This is like the pioneering way to do it.
And it's particularly, it's so easy to spawn new instances
and run things like this.
And yeah, it's completely isolated.
So this is great.
This is up and running and it's running
on the fly.io hardware, on the sprites.dev hardware,
not on Anthropix hardware and certainly not on my computer.
We will let it do its thing.
And I will report back hopefully
when we have a market data review.md.