Okay tons of cool stuff just happened and it's happened too fast but let me let me quickly recap
what I just happened. So first of all I used one of the the pro tips that we went through in week
two which is to press ctrl o to look at the full conversation to see what was going on and to
satisfy myself that indeed most of the tests passed some failed and it correctly accounted
for that. So that was a nice thing to do. Next up I asked it to push its changes to github and that
didn't work because we're not logged into github here and it told me you have to log into github
with gh auth login something that we just covered I think yesterday uh no no earlier today so I I
stopped claude code with a ctrl c twice I did gh auth login and it spawned a window on my computer
even though we're in the in the cloud I logged into github and then we were logged into github
I then typed claude to go back into claude code but but the conversation was started again from
the beginning and I just typed slash resume and remember from from the beginning of week two
that slash resume just takes us back to where we were and I could just say you could see I
said right here okay I've logged you into github but please try now and sure enough it made uh it
made it already made a branch it then pushed that branch to github and it told me it's it's created
a pull request and this is now ready for my review on github let's go take a look so here it
is here is the finally repo there is indeed a market data review let's compare it let's take a
look at it uh here it is it's got this market data review.md there is all of the information
including some of the problems with it uh and so let's say create a pull request and let's merge it
confirm the merge
and we are done fantastic well now I'm I'm on a roll here I'm enjoying the fact that we're
operating in the cloud like this and we can just keep going so I can say okay I've merged
please uh switch to mass domain and do a pull and do a pull
then please um then then please uh carry out all the fixes and improvements
that you've documented in the uh the review file keep working until all tests pass
all tests pass and the product the market data the market data back end is ready
then uh push your new branch
to github that's it I'm running that it's all gonna run in the cloud again on sprites.dev
in a YOLO world where it can do whatever it wants because we know we've got it nicely
sandboxed it's not touching my computer it can't do damage to me so there we go this is
so efficient because there's no more of this permissions approval nonsense it's all running
it's gonna do its thing and I will check back in when we have a working market data back end
and I tell you it's just been the most amazing experience sitting here watching this happening
I haven't approved anything it's been working and working fixing bugs one by one rerunning the
tests more passing reporting on problems and then at the end it created a branch it submitted the
the the push everything just happening uh and uh it's yeah it's created the PR it's ready for me
to review it and I've got this sense that it's super productive and lots are going on lots of
things going on and yet it's also secure it's happening in a way that is totally sandboxed
so it really feels like I've got the best of both which is a great feeling and I continued a
conversation with Claude I gave it a bit of feedback on the changes that are made and made
some more changes there's now a PR that's ready for me to to review here we go and we're going to
have the PR to merge this in and merge and confirm merge and this is fixed and it also incorporated
the extra change I asked as well and so everything is now included in and it's all successfully done
that is finished uh so uh we we have successfully carried out a bunch of work in our remote sandbox
courtesy of sprites.dev and one final point to make on this is that you don't need to just use
this for Claude you could use this of course for Codex for OpenCode for whichever one you have
picked it is ideal for running in a sandbox regardless of your platform and with that
that's enough for today to remind you one more time the three different approaches that we used
today in blue the first thing we did is using the built-in sandbox which is a sort of cheap
and cheerful way of basically like having your own docker container it's like a lightweight os
level Claude code built sandboxing running on your machine we did that it was easy in purple
this is where you take advantage of Anthropix remote running remote execution with with sandbox
is built in and there's a bunch of different ways of doing it some of them didn't work for me but
but will be working by now you should try them but one of the ones some of the ones that did
work was using the web interface using the mobile app which was cool and then the coolest of all
was going to get github putting in an issue it could also be like a pr and then and tagging Claude
and watching it like pick up that issue running it in the Anthropix remote box and then just just
raising the change at the end of it uh pushing its its branch amazing and then in yellow after
doing all of that we looked at a completely different approach which is when we don't use
Anthropix in the cloud we use a third party in this case the company fly.io that has this this
offering sprites.dev we use that it's it's one of the new ones that's that's really fast really easy
to use and it gives you like a command line interface which is actually remoting into
something running on the cloud but we could treat it as if it was a my own machine and it was a bit
confusing because i was running it within vs code so it really felt like it was on my machine and we
could interact with it we could sign into github remotely we could sign into Claude and then we
could carry out activities and we could be in YOLO mode running really efficiently but feeling very
secure as we did and that was the the final approach the yellow approach running on a third
party cloud sandbox and so with that i promised you a juicy day and hopefully you agree it was a
juicy day tomorrow large codebases a big area of concern from people when they're working with
coding agents how does it perform on a big codebase we're going to cover that but also i'm
going to throw some spicy stuff in the mix you know spice it up tomorrow as you will see and
then this is going to be a kind of crescendo because the day after is all about the swarms
and orchestrators that's that's all the rage at the moment before we land on our capstone
okay see you tomorrow for now take a moment to wallow in the fact that you are 80 percent
through 20 percent left to go before you have really mastered coding agents see you tomorrow