This is the start of the crescendo towards the finale of this program.
This is week three, day three, another purple day, another core learning day of skills.
And this is the day when we look at what it takes to build
large code bases, working with big teams, working together with platforms like
Claude Code and Codex and OpenCode and so on, professional coding agents in large teams.
And originally, that was going to be all I was going to cover today.
I was going to have a whole day to talk about large team work and I had some stuff prepared
and I was thinking we would dive in and take a big open source repo and kind of work on it.
But what I sort of realized is that we've already covered all of the foundational skills.
So this is more about summarizing and packaging it all up and explaining the do's and don'ts.
And that would be boring to be an entire day, especially this late in the game.
We're not up for a boring day like that. I can cover that material quite quickly.
And then, and then I've got some spicy topics,
some spicy things to throw into the mix to keep things sizzling.
So prepare yourself, be prepared for some spice.
Let's get through the large code based workflow, some good stuff,
some vegetables to get through first, and then we will bring on the fun.
All right, let's get started.
I'm going to start with another recap.
And I realize this is like the third day in a row of recapping the same material,
but I feel like I gave you a lot to digest on the first day.
Keep the food analogy going.
A lot to digest.
And before we get to the spicy stuff, if I'm not carrying this too much,
it's worth us taking one more moment to look at this.
Slash commands, we know in Cloud Code how you run commands,
and there is a way to configure your own as I showed you.
Although these days, it's more common just to use skills.
And skills, of course, consistent across Cloud Code and Codex.
And I think everyone is really jumping on the skills bandwagon.
To a large extent, they're kind of taking over from MCP as being
the way that we like to build functionality into these coding agents.
Then multi-agents, which is just this idea of running lots of Cloud Code at once,
or maybe kicking off Codex to run as we did, which was really cool.
Or now we know how to throw into that,
like running multiple Clawds that might be on the internet, like out on the cloud.
Perhaps because we just raised a bunch of GitHub issues, and we've tagged Clawd in them.
And that means that Clawd just goes off and does them.
Or perhaps we're using something like Sprites.dev to run on a remote container,
a remote sandbox on the cloud, running lots of Clawds.
All of these things are possible.
Those are multi-agents.
Sub-agents is something that's a bit more contained.
It's when you really delegate one particular task to a sort of sub-instance of Clawd
that just keeps that context, takes care of that, and then returns the results.
And one of the built-in ones that's used a lot is the exploration sub-agent.
They can just sort of go off and dig around a lot of files,
read them all, summarize them, and return that back to the Clawd code context.
So that's multi-agents and sub-agents.
And of course, you can create your own sub-agents and have them able to carry out a task.
Agent teams, we talked about a bit, but we didn't actually use them.
We're going to do them tomorrow.
They are where we start to get a bit more kooky and have things like swarms
and orchestration and stuff like that.
Hooks is something very specific when you want to be able to tie something that's going on,
like Clawd using a tool or something like that,
and have that always triggering, running a command,
or sending a prompt to Clawd, or kicking off a sub-agent.
And you can configure it that way.
And it's used only occasionally, but they do sometimes come packaged in with plugins.
And speaking of, you can also create your own plugins.
As I showed you, you can package up different plugins that can contain
things like skills and sub-agents and commands,
and you can package them up together.
And you can also put them into a marketplace,
and you can then publish that marketplace,
and other people can bring in your marketplace,
and then choose to add in your different plugins.
So that is how you'd create a plugin.
Not something you'd do every day,
but something you might do as part of a larger project, as we'll get to today.
So that's the quick recap on the different Pro features that we covered on Week 3, Day 1.
And then yesterday, we had such an interesting time looking at sandboxing.
It's a very important topic when you're thinking about being able to do more YOLOing,
kick off Clawd to do more,
but there are serious security risks doing that on your computer with your file system,
with your network access, running shell scripts on your computer.
That's where sandboxes come in.
And built into Clawd is the native sandbox,
and it's also built into some other tools like we saw in Cursor.
But in Clawd Code, it's just slash sandbox,
and then you're running in a lightweight native sandbox.
But then we also found out all about using managed Clawd on the web.
And you could have Clawd on the web and just through a web browser kick it off.
You could do it through a mobile app.
You can have it so that it's hooked into GitHub,
so that a GitHub action, you tag Clawd,
and Clawd just goes away and does the work.
And then you find that there's a branch that's been pushed.
There's a PR ready for you with the change made just because you tagged Clawd. It's amazing.
And so, yeah, obviously, I hope you shared in my joy with that.
And I hope you've been trying it out because it's really great.
The thing I didn't get to do yesterday, but you hopefully did,
is just that simple trick of putting an ampersand before a command to Clawd,
which means don't run this here.
Take this whole conversation so far,
push it out onto the internet and run it in a remote Clawd,
and then get back the answer.
It's really amazing that you could do that.
I guess you don't get back the answer.
It runs remotely.
And then you probably saw you could do slash tasks to come and look at them.
So that is a really cool feature of Clawd Code on the web.
And then there is third-party sandboxes.
It's a bit of an up-and-coming feature.
I showed you Sprites.dev that I'm super impressed with.
Just as they say, it is really, really quick.
And it's just very easy then to run on YOLO mode,
on the Clawd, on a fast box.
And so it is stateful in that you can just come back to it.
It's exactly where you left it.
And again, it comes up really, really fast.
And it's got everything just as you left it.
So you can use it as a little home away from home.
And that's really amazing for developing.
And the fact that Clawd Code runs in the terminal like that
means that it's just so convenient.
You just run it there in the terminal remotely.
And you have access to your Clawds wherever you are.
So that is Sprites.dev.
I absolutely love it.
And I hope you are impressed with that too.
And here I am back in VS Code again in the finally repo.
And I've got two terminal screens.
One of them is just a terminal as usual,
normal terminal in the finally directory.
This one here says Sprite on it.
This is just the same one as I had yesterday.
And it's weird that it looks like
this is just a terminal like any other.
But of course, this is actually connected to my remote box,
my Sprite box out there somewhere.
And I actually kept going yesterday.
I couldn't resist.
I couldn't stop.
It was the end of the recording, the end of the day.
But I just had to keep going.
I asked it to do one more thing.
I asked it to update all of its documentation
to have one summary document
because I thought that would be nicer.
And then I also asked it to make a little demo
called Market Data Demo
so that I could see for myself
that it was actually doing something and working.
And I asked it to push that, which of course it did.
And I then came to my local machine here.
And I already did this.
I did like a Git pull
so that the latest code would come down to my computer.
And then I thought, all right,
now it's time to try out this demo.
Let's see what it looks like.
So I asked it for a demo
that could run in a terminal like this,
like not a fancy graphical demo
that could prove that the market data simulator was working
and able to generate market data.
So I cd backend,
and then I wanted to go uv run market data demo.
That's what I should be able to do.
Let's see what happens. Whoa.
Wow.
So take that in for a second.
So you're seeing a bunch of tickers here.
Price is changing here.
This is the change appearing in red and green
and things happening.
And these spark lines is like a text-based graph
of the movement of these stock tickers.
And yeah, come on.
This is fantastic.
This is all like zero shot stuff, as they say,
which means this isn't based on it not working
and then me giving feedback and then it working.
This is just the demo that I asked for,
just working first time,
pushed to GitHub, just like that.
So I absolutely love it.
So I present this to you,
and hopefully you'll be able to get similar kinds of things
by asking for a demo just like this.