Claude Agent SDK was sizzle number one but I have another sizzle lined up for you and it's to show
you CoWork. CoWork is another product by Claude, by Anthropic, and it is basically taking Claude
code and that whole agentic experience that we tech people get to have and offering it to business
people or to anyone that wants to use Claude Code's magic for things other than coding.
That's what CoWork is about Claude CoWork and I want to show it to you now and this is still
like an early release of it in research preview and maybe by the time you're seeing this it's
already gone through a few iterations so you might be more familiar with it but let's do a
quick sizzle let's have a look at it. You start by going to claude.com slash product slash CoWork
link in the resources and then you download Claude to install it on your Mac or Windows box
and I'll see you when you have it installed. And of course this is just the usual Claude desktop
app which you may already have if you don't then the first time you open it will look like this
Claude for Mac for me and maybe Claude for Mac for you maybe Claude for Windows. Fastest way to
talk with Claude I'm going to press get started it's going to want me to log in I'm going to come
in here I'm going to continue with Google that's my Google account continue and then back we come
and we're signed on the usual OAuth flow and then I will just say it's giving me the
instructions that allow me to have shortcut keys and here we are in something that looks very
similar to the web interface and is in fact of course the desktop app we are on chat which is
the normal way that you might chat with Claude like Claude.ai but you'll see there are some other
tabs here it's worth pointing out there is of course a code tab which looks I'll make this
lesson bigger which looks very much like the one that was that was using Claude code on the web
looked like and it is of course also going to be connecting to the managed service of Claude
on the web and then there is co-work the new tab in the middle let's knock something off your list
setting up Claude's workspace so again what we're doing here is we are connecting to Claude
running on the cloud for it to do a task for us and you can see that that it's got some some
things that it can do like optimize my week organize my screenshots it's the the sorts of
things that it's good at doing it's like Claude codes kind of to-do lists and abilities but
applied to everyday kinds of tasks so the sorts of things that co-work can do is stuff like
reorganizing files like it can look at images it can do stuff it's also got the ability to have
plugins customized with plugins and you can see from the way this is organized the anthropic
official plugins and so on there's like plug-in marketplaces it's all a very nice mirror from
what we used to with Claude code and this has stuff like like looking digging through data
looking at finance stuff legal things like contract review we know a tool that can that
can build legal documents uh nda triage uh so there's lots of useful things in here let's go
for something that might be useful for me right now okay so i'm going to click on this button
work in a folder right here and i'm going to go to my desktop and there's a folder called receipts
and i'm going to work in this folder allow it to change files in there and now um in the folder
that i've shared with you there are a bunch of receipts they are all pdfs of images
please uh review these and make me an expenses report as an excel file expenses
dot xlsx and that's what we will do that would be handy there's like 12 of them in there
it would like to access it we'll give it access to that and off it goes there's stuff happening
over here let me start by reading the excel skill and checking what receipts you have
off it goes things are happening 12 pdf receipts let me read them all to extract the details
so we will let this happen look at all these things going on stuff happening there uh and uh
it's going through and reading them at one at a time and i will see you in a minute when it's
hopefully done well a lot happened there it chugged away it did lots of processing it had
some problems with the pdfs because it realized it needed to read them in like images and it did
some stuff but it's just finished after i think about five or ten minutes of thinking and in my
receipts folder a new file has appeared called expenses dot xlsx and if i launch that this thing
comes up and sure enough it has like it's a nicely formatted expenses report with 1212 receipts in
there and with all of these different bits of visual audio equipment and subscriptions and then
with a total and a total amount and it all seems to be good uh and so yes that is something that
that uh i might have had to have done myself it's from the past so i did that myself and so i know
that it's painful and this is an example of the kind of task that is quite easy for co-work so
there you have it this is taking the claude code that we know and that is so helpful for us
as engineers and allowing people to use it for everyday tasks like making expenses spreadsheets