And now the third of our sizzles is OpenClaw. OpenClaw is massively hyped at the moment and
blown up and I personally rather suspect that it's going to die down a bit. I could be completely
wrong, I might be like someone that's saying this chat GPT thing, it's not gonna last but
yeah I might as well just throw it into the mix of some sizzle. It's not of course related to
coding agents, it's a big hyped thing but just to give you a sense of what it is so you've got the
context, it is still sort of it's first of all it was itself vibe coded and it's very much on
the same theme of appreciating the power of these coding agents like Claw Code and imagining rather
like co-work what happens if we apply this to every day beyond development and OpenClaw is
taking it even further, it's described as your personal AI, it's about really trying to to be
your sidekick, something that could be there for you and it's also considered something that's
a bit on the dangerous side because you run it on your computer, you typically give it access
to everything, you connect it to everything, that's why it has its power but with great power
comes responsibility and comes risk and that's why some security professionals are very concerned
about OpenClaw and one way that you could run it of course is in a sandbox as we discovered
a couple of days ago. Anyway OpenClaw isn't completely relevant for coding except for
seeing the potential of this stuff so I will just quickly give you a perspective on it
so that we get our sizzle and then we will move swiftly on. So here is OpenClaw and you go to
openclaw.ai to see this page, OpenClaw of course was originally called Clawdbot, spelled C-L-A-W-D
Clawdbot and apparently they had a letter from from Anthropic and so they changed their name
to Maltbot which was still a sort of riff off this the the lobster idea but that they decided
didn't didn't sound, it was hard to say and so they changed it third time to OpenClaw which is
what it's called now unless it's changed its name again but I doubt it. So OpenClaw is what we've
got and you can install it with a one-liner that's the one line for Mac OS if you're on a
Windows PC then this would be your one line if you're on a PowerShell or this in a CMD but you'll
probably be on a PowerShell but I'm going to go back to being on a Mac and I will run this now
in a terminal and one of the things they say is that if you don't know how to use a terminal
then perhaps you're not ready to use OpenClaw because it's it's designed for people that know
enough about what's going on to feel like you you you know the risks you're signing up for
and of course the the main thing as it says here that that that it runs on your computer that the
way that you interact with it is through a chat app it's like got a this native chat first experience
you can be in WhatsApp or in Telegram talking to your sidekick to your Clawdbot it's got it's got
memory it remembers what's going on it can drive a browser it can use anything on your computer
and it's got a whole raft of plugins that you could click into it and therein lies many of
its powers so here look I brought up a terminal this is just a normal Mac terminal I'm going to
paste in that command to install it on my Mac let's give this a try it's doing uh doing a bunch
of uh stuff and uh OpenClaw installer I'm the reason your shell history looks like a hacker
movie montage okay and I will let it do its thing I will see you in a sec and so I love this
it says uh OpenClaw installed successfully the lobster has landed your terminal will never
be the same let's make this nice and big for you uh and then we get this uh OpenClaw security
please read it's a hobby project still in beta expect sharp edges it can read files run actions
a bad prompt can trick it to doing unsafe things uh run an OpenClaw security audit regularly
you must read the security stuff I understand this is powerful and inherently risky continue
defaulting to no we'll go to yes uh onboarding mode quick start and we will do the quick start
okay and now we get to the models and we start with choosing a model auth provider and it's got
a bunch of them and I think we've we've uh we've got enough of of using anthropic we let's switch
to open ai for a bit and use uh oh also I'm going to select this uh we can choose whether we want
to do a chat gpt oauth or whether we want to use an api key this this is like an in browser login
and that is the one that we will try so I will do this and it jumps me over to here continue with
google sign into codex with chat gpt continue successful return to your terminal to continue
and now it's saying default model keep current we'll use gpt 53 codex that sounds good to me
select a channel quick start so I'd say let's go with the telegram let's do telegram telegram
bot token open telegram and now it's telling me to to do this and I have telegram so I'm going to
open telegram I'm going to chat I'm going to select that I want to chat with at bot father
I'm going to run slash new bot it's going to make a token and I'm going to copy it in here and then
I'm going to keep going and I'm going to do that offline so that I keep that that secret and I'll
see you back here in a sec okay so I did that I set up my telegram bot following the instructions
and my id the token is just off the top of the screen so I shrunk it down and then I've said yes
I want to configure skills now my preferred node manager is npm and I can now install skills
different things to do stuff that might be useful for me and you can see all the different things it
can do by scrolling through here and get a good sense it could turn on and off my light bulbs
it could do all these different things and let me see what we want to have it be able to do today
okay so I've only chosen one simple skill the open ai whisper which seems like a nice easy
one it's got no api key it just means that there'll be access to speech to text so we'll
let that install and then we'll see what else we can set up okay so I went through a setup process
I had to answer a few questions it wanted to know what it would be called and I called it
sidekick kind of boring it wanted to know a vibe and it wanted an emoji I'm definitely not cool
enough to be using this product so I tried my best and then hooked it up to a few things and
now it's connected to telegram so I can chat with it over telegram and I could be doing this on my
phone I could be doing this as I am on my computer on my telegram app but this is going to allow me
now to have a conversation with my sidekick running on my computer okay let's give this a try
I'm pressing start let's have a conversation I'm here Edward sidekicks ready okay uh please look
up tesla stock price if uh it um went up today
okay please play me something upbeat
otherwise something depressing okay let's give it that instruction I'm wanting it to go and
do a web search I want it to understand what I mean figure this out and then play me music
how's it going to do that through telegram or something okay we have music we have something
playing it went up today and so it's playing upside down by diana ross and how's it playing
it it's playing it because it's controlling spotify on my computer it's activated spotify
and it's playing diana ross and here you can see the telegram uh chat I was having alongside
open claw that was running on my computer in this terminal ui looking a lot like clawed code
in a way and it's got a message it's replying to it it's decided it's looked up the stock price
it went up today upbeat is the decision it made a choice about what track to play I left that up to
its autonomy its discretion it put on diana ross it controlled spotify and that's what you heard
playing so you know that that gives you a sense of what what this is all about people are excited
because you can drive things from just from your your chat interface it comes to you it can it can
wake up and alert you about things it can be integrated across all of the capabilities on
your computer it can drive windows it can look things up on the web so it it can be incredibly
autonomous and it really brings the power of clawed code and the cli tools again that we're
used to as engineers and it brings them to people personally as their personal sidekick okay so that
brings today to a wrap today really was a light day we did cover the big project concerns of just
the right way to approach a big repo and we will touch on that again tomorrow when we when things
go really crazy and then after doing that we just had some light relief with a few things for you to
look at like like the good old claude agent sdk which is which is an important way to drive
claude code programmatically and then we looked at co-work taking what this these exciting tooling
and bringing it to the professional world and then open claw which is bringing the same kind
of capability to a personal world to have everyone have their own personal sidekick that you could
control from telegram from whatsapp and have it be able to control your computer your lights your
music whatever you want and that that is open claw i know i just gave you a teaser of it because that's
not really what we're covering on this course but i did want you to see it and have a feel for it
all right tomorrow is a massive day tomorrow is when we go into swarms we look at teams we're
going to look at a few really interesting way to orchestrate multiple agents collaborating
together in unison to achieve a bigger task and that will lead us all the way to the capstone
and with that amazingly 87 is where we're at massive congrats get ready for two big days ahead
see you tomorrow