At the start of our three weeks together, I told you to expect a rollercoaster.
And here's the thing. We, on this rollercoaster journey, we have just reached that point
when the rollercoaster has got to the very, very top, and you're up there at the top,
and you're looking down, and we're about to take the plunge.
Prepare for the plunge. Prepare for week three, day four. This is a big day.
It's another purple day. It's a day of core skills.
It's the day when we move into the world of swarms and orchestrators.
The time when we go crazy. And it's all about the stages seven and eight
of the Steve Yegge chart that we went through a couple of weeks ago now.
We've already got quite comfortable with the idea that you can run multiple Claude instances.
We've done that a bit. We haven't done that in a massive way,
because it's all sort of leading up to this.
But for sure, you've probably experimented with running Claude a few times,
and we had things like that experiment when we had Claude running,
and we had Codex doing the code review.
And so we've seen all of this happening.
And of course, we've worked with sub-agents a fair bit too.
Well, this is the moment when we hit stages seven and eight.
This is the moment when we start to have tons of agents running,
which is what you think of as a swarm,
when you have like a huge number of them all doing stuff.
Everything's going on. It seems mad. It's chaos.
And then stage eight is when you're like,
okay, maybe we can reel this in.
We can control the chaos by giving the different agents some structure,
by having some in charge of others, by trying to coordinate the work,
but having the LLMs manage the process.
That's what orchestration is about.
And that's what we're going to be doing today.
And as we look between stages seven and eight, swarms versus orchestration,
I don't know that there's necessarily a binary.
We are at this point and we're at that point.
The different solutions we'll be looking at are somewhere on that continuum,
but between being sort of wild swarm with no structure
and extremely organized, structured orchestration.
And where you are on that continuum depends a bit on the choices that you make,
how you set it up and how crazy you want to go. As we will see.
All right, we're going to be doing a few different approaches
and I'm going to start right away by looking at Claude's agent teams,
which is the one thing from, I guess, the day one of this week
that we said we'd come back to.
Now's the time. We're coming back to it right here.
So Claude agent teams, first of all, is an experimental feature as of right now.
By the time you watch this, maybe it's matured.
Maybe it's no longer just an experimental feature.
But for me, it is.
This is brand new and I'll be going through the experimental side of it.
And maybe you'll look at the docs and see that some of this has become a bit more firm.
But first of all, what are agent teams?
They are ways that you can have multiple Claude code instances,
multiple different Claude codes that are being coordinated in some way.
One of them is acting as the team lead.
It is in charge of the whole process.
And its job is to assign out tasks and manage the collaboration between them
in order to achieve a goal.
And then the others, the teammates, they're able to work independently
and they're able to interact with each other so they can send each other messages.
And you, as the human in the loop, you can interact with them directly as well.
You don't need to go through the lead.
And this is a massive distinction from sub-agents.
With sub-agents, you can't send a message to a sub-agent.
It just exists in order to serve the main Claude code.
And it doesn't really work independently.
It only persists for the duration of its task and then its history.
Whereas in this case, these things called teammates,
their teammates, they are all separate Claude codes that are running.
Okay, so under what circumstances would you make use of Claude agent teams
instead of, say, sub-agents?
We'll have a direct comparison in a moment.
But here are some examples of use cases that work well for Claude teams.
So one of them is if, and this is a sort of simple one that you can imagine,
if you want to research a ton of different things,
like you want to head off and look, you want to look at Wikipedia,
and you also want to look at Stack Overflow,
and you also want to look at three other places,
then you could just have a multiple of these team members go off,
do their research independently, working on it,
maybe exchanging information between them,
and then come back with all of the results.
And that's something that you can also use sub-agents for,
but this is a nice kind of use case.
But perhaps a better one, if I may,
is a case where you have independent modules of your system,
and you've got an objective,
and you can see a way that different Claude codes could work independently.
And indeed, you could just spawn multiple terminals and run Claude
and have them run independently,
but you would prefer them to be able to communicate
and have some shared structure.
Now, they can communicate anyway through .md files
if you did have them as separate terminals,
but it would be a little bit flaky.
It would depend a lot on who's writing what to which file
rather than reading them again.
So this way, you could have different Claude code instances
working on different modules,
but still working in lockstep,
still having a channel of communication.
And then the other way is kind of similar,
but it's saying rather than dividing them vertically
into different areas of responsibility,
you could divide them horizontally by layer,
by coding layer,
like you could have a front-end engineer,
back-end engineer, LLM engineer,
responsible for different areas of your system.
And that does translate quite nicely
to the way that you sometimes organize humans
in a software engineering team,
that you can do it by area, by feature,
by feature area of your system,
or you can do it into a front-end team
and a back-end team and so on.
And, you know, I always hesitate
before ascribing too much human-like responsibility to agents,
but you can see how this works quite well
in terms of having separate responsibilities
that cloud code instances can work on independently
without too much overlap.
And you're probably getting the idea
that there's a lot of experimentation involved
in getting agent teams to work well.
There's not necessarily one right answer.
It needs some balance.
You're ideally looking to be able to give
separate responsibilities to cloud agents
so that they can work independently
and still have some benefit to communication
between the agents so they can collaborate,
but not so much communication
that they start to grind down
and they're churning with lots of backwards and forwards.
So you're looking to strike that balance.
And Anthropic's website is really good on this.
It's got some very clear instructions
and they may have changed since I'm doing this.
It's probably worth a look.
It's got this nice table in there
that compares sub-agents to agent teams,
these two techniques.
And it's pretty clear that they are very different
and they each have their place,
sub-agents where they have their own context,
they return it to the caller,
the communication is only back to their main agent.
The main agent manages all the work.
They have focused tasks
and they basically summarize the results back
so they're quite efficient from a token point of view.
They can cause more tokens to be spent themselves,
but they're relatively efficient.
Agent teams, they have their own full context window
that is completely independent.
They don't return it to the caller.
They can message the other teammates independently.
They have a shared task list.
There is one task list that is managed
by the overall, by the main Claude code,
and they coordinate their items on the task list.
They're best for when there is complex work
that does require a level of collaboration,
but not too much.
And they can be expensive.
They can cause a lot of tokens to be spent.
So you need to be aware of that.
And look at that last bullet there.
Use sub-agents when you need quick,
focused workers that report back.
Use agent teams when teammates need to share findings,
challenge each other, and coordinate on their own.
Okay, there are five instructions
that we will go through now.
It's time for us to do this.
Five steps to making the Claude agent teams work.
First of all, we need to change
settings.json for the project.
We need to tell it that we are going to enable
Claude code experimental agent teams.
You might not need to do this
because it might then be fully live
without needing this flag, but we do.
There's another field as well called teammate mode.
And there are two modes.
And one of them, in process,
works on all computers, on Mac and PC.
And it just means that all of the agents
report back in the same screen.
And you can flip between them
by pressing shift up and down.
And that's what we'll use.
There is a cooler approach called Teamux.
But that only works on Macs and Linux
when you have extra stuff installed.
And so I'm not going to do it.
But if you wish, you could try that.
And when you do that,
your screen splits into different sections.
And you can see each of the different agents
in a different section.
And that's pretty cool.
So you might want to do that
if you want to see that yourself.
You have to change in process to Teamux
and you have to have the Teamux installed
or be using something called iTerm2
if you know what that is.
So this is what we're going to put in settings.json.
And this should work on all platforms.
And then it's just as simple as prompting Claude
to say create an agent team to blah, blah, blah.
And you can give it a lot of detail
and tell it how the agent should be made up
or the team should be made up
or you can just give it the instruction.
You can then press shift tab
to turn it into delegate mode.
That's something worth doing
to make sure that the main agent
doesn't just start handling the tasks itself.
And you can also, if necessary,
prompt it, wait for your teammates
to complete their tasks before proceeding
to stop it diving in and doing work itself.
Anthropic mentions that that's a common problem.
And then shift up and down
is how you flip between the different teammates.
And when you're done,
you send a command,
ask the blah teammate to shut down
as a way to tell the main agent
that it should shut down one of the team members.
And then clean up the team
is a general command to stop everything.
So we need to know these commands,
these are the instructions
for successfully running an agent team in Cloud Code.
And as three final bits of advice
before we go and do this,
we should invest in cloud.md.
That gets loaded into the context for everything.
And so it's our opportunity to make sure
that all the agents start with the right information.
And we need to expect this to be pricey.
If you try and use free models for this,
you could give it a shot,
but I imagine it's just not going to be reliable.
So if you're not comfortable with the cost,
just watch me use this as a learning experience
from seeing someone else doing it.
If you're okay to go for this,
then do expect a cost.
Watch your costs.
Stop it if you ever become uncomfortable.
And also to add salt to the wound,
you do need to be willing to rerun the whole thing.
It might go off the rails.
You might need to stop it, go back in Git,
and then just run it another time,
maybe tweaking the instructions.
This is highly experimental.
It's something that is incredibly powerful.
It's also unpredictable and a bit chaotic,
and it can take several attempts.
Okay, with that, I hope you're excited
and maybe a little tiny bit nervous.
Let's go to VS Code.
Let's try Claude agent teams for real.