Welcome back to VS Code.
We're going to start by cleaning things up so we're in great shape.
I want to just check what's in .cloud.
You can see that we have agents is empty,
commands is empty, skills,
we just have our Cerebra skill which is great.
We want to keep that.
Settings.json is empty,
settings.local.json says what it's allowed to do.
Okay, and the sandbox is currently off.
That's good because we want to keep everything as vanilla,
as simple as possible.
.github contains the actions.
If we wanted to tag Cloud, that's fine.
We're not going to be doing that right now.
Okay, we've got the market data summary at this point. That's great.
I also want to go into Cloud
and find out what kind of plugins we have enabled,
what MCP we have enabled.
We want to make sure that everything is nice and vanilla
because we don't want to confuse things
if we're going to go crazy with agent teams. So here we go.
I'll bring up a terminal and we will go into Cloud. Here it is.
Let's just have a look at the plugin situation.
See what we've got installed right now.
We've got no plugins or MCP servers installed.
That seems pretty good.
Okay, let's go back.
Let's go into skills.
Sorry, I need the slash. Skills.
See what we've got.
We've got the one skill, Cerebras inference. That's it. Love it.
And let's go into MCP,
see what we have in our MCP servers.
No MCP servers as we just saw. Very good.
Okay, we are now going to install a few plugins
that might be useful for our agents to have.
And I want to avoid plugins that themselves spawn sub-agents
or we're going to lose control.
So I'm going for the simple ones.
I'm not going for the really sophisticated ones
like feature dev or something like that.
So we go back to plugin.
Let's take a look at them.
So front-end design is one that just adds some information
so that it makes production grade front-ends
that don't have that characteristic LLM look and feel.
And so I think this is a good one for us to have.
Let's put that in in the project scope.
So I will do that.
We will press enter and we've installed that.
And let's go back to plugin again,
see what else we could have here.
So context seven, we know that. That's great.
That adds all the information about current APIs.
Let's add that in as well.
So we will do that.
We will also install it in the project scope.
And then just one more plugin.
So the code simplifier seems like a great thing to have,
but again, I feel like that's going to be
installing a sub-agent.
That's going to be too confusing.
And I just think I might want to include this playwright one
which is going to allow the agent to be able to spawn
a browser and run playwright tests, which is pretty cool.
So I do want to install that one.
Let's do that for collaborators
on this project project scope. Okay.
So we do now have those plugins.
You remember, we need to restart Claude code
for those to take effect.
But first I'm going to come out of here
and I'm going to go to the claude.md
and just get a sense of where we are with that.
Make sure that we're happy that this is giving us
the full lay of the land.
So it's saying that the document
is planned.md and included here.
Let's just add to this now to give it a bit more context. Okay.
So I'm coming into claude.md.
I'm going to take that sentence there
and replace it with this.
The key document is planned.md included and filled below.
The market data components already completed.
It's summarized in this file
with more details in that folder.
Consult these docs only when required.
The remainder of the platform is still to be developed.
So that shows you the key distinction
between using the at tag
that will insert the entire contents
of planned.md in context
versus giving a link like this,
which is giving it like a path.
We should probably put this inside single ticks
so that it knows it's like a path like that.
Come some like that.
And now it's going to look into these only if it needs to.
It's a bit like the way that we build skills files.
It means that it's going to only progressively
add these to the context when required naturally.
Okay, I would say that's enough for the updated claude.md.
Okay, and now just some quick Git housekeeping.
I'm bringing back up my terminal
that's come out of Claude code.
Just clear the screen.
I'm just going to do a quick Git status to see where I am. Great.
I'm going to check everything in.
I'm going to do a Git commit.
Git commit and call it ready for teams and Git push.
Okay, all those changes are now committed and done.
And we have a good baseline point
that we can use for going crazy.
Okay, we're now going to create a separate branch in Git
so that we can work off to one side
in case we need to come back here easily.
So I'm going to do Git checkout minus B, agent teams,
a new branch called agent teams.
Switch to a new branch, agent teams.
If you need to know more about Git,
look at the resources for that.
All right, and now we are going to change
our settings.json.
Are you ready for this?
I'm adding into the settings.json some more settings.
Let's have a look.
It's missing a comma there that I will,
that was wrong in the slide as well.
You may have noticed it's missing a comma,
obviously I will add that in.
So yeah, this is now saying we want an environment variable,
Claude code experimental agent teams to be set to one.
The team mode is going to be in process. Save that.
Okay, so we are now ready to go.
It's when we start Claude, it's going to start in this mode.
Hold onto your hat, let's do this.
Okay, so in I go, into Claude.
Here is Claude, everybody.
Opus 4.6, we hopefully have our settings done.
We are ready to go.
We're ready to do the command
that's going to kick off our team.
Well, actually, let's just quickly do a slash usage
to see where we stand.
We can come back to this.
We've currently got 0% usage,
just as of today's quota.
And I'm at 8% of the week's quota.
I'm going to write that down.
That's for all models.
So it's 0%, 8% and 2%.
Okay, that's interesting.
We'll see where this ends up being.
And let's also do a slash context
to see how we're looking at the context.
You'll see, gosh, there's lots of playwright related tools.
I'm wondering whether that was a mistake to add that in,
but it's only a couple of these.
And then a lot of memory used up from our plan, which is good.
Excellent, I think we're ready to go.
Let me paste in the command.
I want to create an agent team to build the entire project.
Team members, I'm specifying.
You don't need to, you can let it choose its own,
or you can choose them by stating them.
A front-end engineer to work on the front-end,
a back-end engineer,
a database engineer for all database code,
an LLM engineer for the calls,
the LLMs hopefully using the Cerebra skill.
And all engineers should work on their unit tests,
but there should also be an integration tester
and also a DevOps engineer for the Docker container.
Now, I was tempted to also add in a code reviewer agent
to check that code is simple and clear
and give feedback back to the agents.
But on reflection,
I feel like that might be a step too far
in terms of just too much noise,
too much chattiness between the agents.
We're introducing something
which is going to require conversation
with every single agent and more backwards and forwards.
And I feel like that's going to just add more noise
than we would like.
So that's probably going too far that way.
Anyway, that's why I made this decision.
We're going to give it a try
and we know we might have to do this several times over
to get it right.
And before I kick it off,
I'm going to shift tab to go through the modes,
accept edits on, plan mode on.
We want to accept edits on,
and then I'm going to kick this off. Here we go.
Off it goes, accept edits on.
Now, I think I remember that shift tab should also,
well, let's watch what it does.
It's starting by exploring the current project state,
then it's going to create the team and then the tasks. Exciting.
I am a bit anxious, I have to admit.
Now, I thought that shift tab
was also supposed to put on delegate mode. Let's see.
No, it's just, I'm just going to leave it on this,
accept edits on.
The anthropic docs might also be
not always completely up to date,
so I don't know whether to take it with a pinch of salt.
Okay, so it's still exploring the states.
We're waiting to see once it's done that,
if it's going to then launch all the teams,
in which case I've got my fingers ready
to do shift up and down
so that I can flip between the different agents.
It's keeping on going.
I think I'll probably put you on pause
and come back in a second
when it's starting to spawn the team.
Okay, it's all happening.
It took about five minutes to think things through,
and now it is spawning team members.
And you can see that there is a DB engineer
and a front-end engineer happening.
The DB engineer is already building
a SQLite database layer.
There's stuff going on.
I need to make this bigger
to see what's going on here. Lots happening.
Team is launched.
Here is the current setup.
Database engineer, front-end engineer,
and then backend, LLM, DevOps,
and integration testing are all waiting
for us, I guess.
Oh yes, look at that, blocked by.
So it's got like a little dependency
project plan going on.
Now let's just try pressing shift
and up and down and see what happens.
I probably have to be clicked in here.
Shift up and down, there we go.
This is how I can,
you can see that it's flipping between
team lead, DB engineer, front-end engineer, and hide.
This is how you can flip between them
and look at each one and what it's doing.
And they are all on the go.
Everything is happening.
Only three so far.
The DB and the front-end,
but I imagine many more to come very shortly.