I should mention now that I've been asked to approve a few things a UV ad from the database
engineer and now creating the next project by the front-end engineer and that's great.
I haven't done dangerously skip permissions which I might have done YOLO mode if I were using the
sandbox that we were looking at before but in this this case it's good that I get to approve these
things as should you because I want to make sure I know what kinds of commands are being run
particularly when we're in this kind of chaotic setup and it's now a few minutes later and the
the first the database engineer has completed the sql setup and so the back-end engineer has been
kicked off and you can now see that that is happening there's a back-end engineer if I do
my shift up and down you can see that we can flip between now the team lead the back-end engineer
and the front-end engineer it's interesting that it is a bit more serial than I was expecting I
guess I had some sense from when I put in that prompt at the beginning that they were all going
to kick off and start working even because you could imagine you could begin the back-end work
before the database is completely finished and so it is quite serial and that does make sense
that is a more structured organized way of doing it that probably leads to better outcomes a bit
less chaotic and more managed so it's probably a good thing to see that and I imagine that by
tweaking that initial prompt I could have encouraged it to try and be a little bit more
put everything in parallel run more concurrently but you'd probably get worse outcomes and I'm
happy to see the back-end engineer is now complete the back-end engineer has done 121 passing all
121 tests are passing it's been marked as complete it's been shut down again a bit more serial than
I was expecting and then spawning the AI engineer now unblocks and in some ways you could also argue
perhaps this is sensing that that the AI the the LLM engineer and the back-end engineer could have
been the same sub-agent although perhaps it's good to preserve some context and keep them as
separate but they didn't need that to run concurrently or at least it was perhaps ill-advised
and certainly our team coordinator felt it was ill-advised to run them concurrently and I notice
I'm pleased to see that it's pointing out that it needs to be through open router Cerebras I'm going
to be interested to see if it ends up using the skill properly as it should and I imagine it will
and it will we will be able to tell from from whether it knows how to assign it to Cerebras
and so this seems to be happening I can see that we've got now oh now we have more agents running
let's take a look we've got the team lead the DevOps engineer the front-end engineer and the
LLM engineer they are all running so for the first time we have four sub-agents not sub-agents four
agents running in our team it's all happening there's just tons going on now uh you can see
that uh the lots of um of different two tool calls happening now it's asking me now whether
it can proceed with running some some tests absolutely I'm going to press two chmod commands
okay so it's wanting to to give um power to run scripts this is a clear case of when I should
press one and not two I'm happy for it to change the the ownership of these scripts to change them
so I can execute them but I want to approve that every time and let's see what's this that one this
is this is for testing I'm happy for to press two for that so making good decisions about whether to
to approve only in this case or always approve is important we see these are all running you can see
how many tool uses have happened already and how many tokens are coming out of these the front-end
engineer 93000 tokens uh lots going on docker build I'm happy for it to be able to do that
uh I'm pressing two for that um that is the devops engineer running that so you can see and and uh
again that's that's fine you can see lots going on I'm approving for each of the different workers
and I see stuff as a docker just just launched so I wasn't running docker uh and it saw that
that was my mistake I should have opened docker it just launched docker uh and uh started it good
good for it amazing and that's definitely an example of something that opus 4.6 could handle
that models couldn't handle in the past that was my mistake um and on it goes see you in a second
okay we're now done with everything except it's explaining just the llm engineer is done the front
end engineer is done we're just waiting for the devops engineer to finish building and then it's
going to pass over to the integration tester and I'm interested I'm a bit concerned that if the
integration tester finds problems how is it going to be able to to delegate back to the the uh the
agents that have completed so that's going to be one to watch out for see how that coordination works
okay everything has now completed except the integration tester and so it is spawning the
integration tester as it says the final agent we'll see how it handles any problems that it has
but that is now the only other agent running except for our our boss our team lead there you
go I just press shift up so I could see that um and uh I remember ctrl t is how I toggle the task
list there's the task list ctrl t toggles the task list off and on and shift up and down is how you
flip between the different team members uh good shortcut keys to know so uh now it's running the
integration tests we'll see how this goes and uh then we uh yeah we'll see what it handles any
problems with the integration tests and then we'll see whether the thing works so it's been
testing for quite a while I have to say it's been going for 11 minutes and I can see here uh the
integration tester found five a pair response mismatches causing a front-end crash and the
the team leads is good catch uh yes fix blah blah blah and it says the integration tester is now
fixing the response format mismatches so I was hoping it was going to be the original front-end
developer that would fix the problems I guess it wants the integration tester to do the fixing
uh I will let it do its thing I'm not going to contradict we will let it finish see where it
gets to see if that was a good pattern or maybe should have prompted it differently at the
beginning or maybe even I should jump in now but for this one I would rather just let it be
let it complete let's see where it gets and that is a wrap so it completed all of the tasks uh
it uh found the bug with the five api responses a minor note the css layer overlap uh but non-blocking
I guess we'll see that to run the app it's got the instructions well we shouldn't need to do that
because there should be oh there we go it says there's a script start mac uh it's finished the
teammate shut down gracefully the team is cleaned up the finally project build is complete six agents
six tasks all done the app is ready to run so there we've got lots of stuff we've got lots of
files changed uh fair enough I think uh it's time for us to try this out okay I'm gonna start a new
terminal window I am going to do scripts slash start mac oh that's not good what have we got here
start uh sorry start underscore mac there we go okay here we go and it's coming up at localhost
tooth 8000 but that didn't seem to run there we go bam okay that's pretty cool this is the market
data watch list on the left you can see that it's flashing we can see everything going on we've got
an ai assistant we've got a portfolio we've got 10000 in cash uh let's see now what do we do we
can do ticker let's let's try and do some uh some buying let's buy some jp morgan stock why not to
buy bam there we go jp morgan has appeared here the heat map shows it at zero this is amazing
uh okay now why is there we go it has just changed the heat map has changed
that trade and this is of course all fake market data that is a negative and now it's a positive
uh that's nice uh as we go into the plus what else should we get from from here let's let's add in
some google stock ticker google quantity and look at that the cell just moved across that's a little
bit of a blip let's buy that now it comes in our portfolio heat map right here uh what happens if
we click on here what does this price chart here give us i'm not sure uh this is this is the
portfolio pnl showing right here this is all pretty cool it's got the right color scheme with the the
my favorite colors but also looking very active this is uh with with perhaps a couple of things
that might be improved uh it looks like we're getting some zero shot success working first time
but now we have to try out the ai assistant okay so let's go over to the ai assistant and say um
please uh add spy to the watch list
see what it does it's thinking about that spy has been added to your watch list and there it is on
the watch list uh it doesn't seem to be changing though that's interesting um okay then uh we'll say
please buy one share of v uh let's see what that does and it just did uh executed purchase of one
share of v at market price bam and there it is on the heat map and this heat map is uh is obviously
like one where uh larger boxes represent more more uh portfolio weight um in dollar terms that's
really cool there's a lot to take in here you can tell i'm slightly frazzled as i try and absorb all
of this this seems to be a bit of an error right here that that this price chart doesn't seem to
fill in um but this is all working it's able to respond here the overall portfolio pnl this line
appears not to be moving but it's pretty good i would say that this is um this is an impressive
setup yeah you can see everything is happening here the portfolio price is adjusting the amount
of cash i've got has come down of course uh it's uh it's looking really excellent um yeah please
give me some trading advice see what it says if we do this uh
your portfolio is cash heavy with small position in google consider rebalancing um uh oh and i
just noticed that the portfolio pnl is it is changing like this that's great uh please do
this for me let's see how that does just giving it a uh a request to do some portfolio rebalancing
everything appears to have stopped that's thinking that's caused it some consternations
there we go sold your two shares of jp morgan to free cash for rebalancing okay fair enough uh i
don't think that was a great move but if what i wanted to do was to bring in more cash into equity
but there we go it's working it's cool it's amazing to see this it definitely has the live dynamic
sense and most importantly it's it's hanging together it's it's uh the functionality is there
it's tested right a couple of quibbles like this section here that seems to be a bit a bit
unawesome other than that i give this high marks how about you okay well i've closed that window
down i'm intrigued to see that i can bring it back up and it just continues where it was just as we'd
specified now what we could do now is go in and fix those various bugs give it some feedback and fix
them but i think it's more interesting for us to give this zero shot idea another try with some
other workflows so let's now stop this server scripts slash stop underscore mac dot shell
it's stopped okay great and now we're going to do a git status and see everything that's in here
there's a lot of stuff that's been built okay now i'm going to do a git add dot that's putting
everything into git uh and uh and into so it's staged for commit let's do another git status
and see what that looks like now lots of things have been set up here uh and let's just make sure
that there's nothing in here that looks concerning it hasn't checked in uh no modules or anything no
everything is correctly gets ignored and there's a docker ignore and there's a dot emv dot example
but not a dot emv file that all seems great um okay then just double checking good then what
we're now going to do is now do a a git push but to this branch we're going to commit and then push
to agent dash teams so git commit minus m uh agent teams v1
git push origin agent teams and off it has gone so that has now been pushed to that branch
agent teams excellent look at what we can do now thanks to the power of git we can do git
check out main and all of our code flips back to where we were before
bam gone okay great now on to the next