Okay so I know the next command is going to be discuss phase but it says what do you want to
build and I'm just going to respond to that question because it says back to where we were.
So please build the entire project everything as described in planning slash plan dot md.
Let's give it that command that's what we want and we may have to do the various gsd
discussing phases and so on but got it we want to put the full trade trading workstation
um that's a solid foundation it says okay it's off so uh we will um let it do its thing so
this market back in what remains is data fully rest apis llm chat an entire front end a few
things to clarify how polished does the front end needs to be for course demo um i uh what do
we think i think we want something really production quality i don't think we want this to
be like a demo thing i mean it is a demo but we want it to be really great production quality
that's what we're gonna say uh for having the llm chat the plan says cerebrus does should the
llm work out of the box without an api mock mode uh keys required um oh wait it works without using
mock real um no i'd say that that's uh it should it should need a key docker how should i build
the docker file and stop start scripts or focus on the app code include docker for sure submit
answers i love this so it's really cool the way that it's interactive and it comes back
us the distinct questions like that that we that we answer i think i have a clear picture build
finally platform end to end uh ready to create project md let's do that okay so it is this guided
process it's more controlled on rails but still with this idea that there's going to be a lot
happening on in parallel so i'm fine for it to do that i'm going to press number two there's
going to be a few a few i think approves as we go um and i will probably uh like make sensible
answers to questions if there's a really interesting one i'll stop but otherwise i
will see you when we made some more progress okay it's been about 20 minutes or something that this
has been chugging for and a lot has gone on and it's now stopped and said v1 requirements
covering database apis front-end llm chat docker and end-to-end tests uh does it look right and
this is another is a good sign that that this is somewhere in between the insanity of of just using
like teams that just go off into the wild and then process that's more on rails and it's
encouraging us to look at a document called requirements and these documents are all in a
folder it's created called dot planning a bit confusing since we called our own one planning
already let's go into dot planning here is requirements dot md and open it up and you'll
see here are the full requirements that it's got and we can just scan through it you can see it's
got lots of bits and pieces that it that it wants to write and test this is super impressive you
can see it's got all of these uh different ids for each part it's given itself a checklist um
lots of stuff going on things that are out of scope the stuff here that's putting in a v2
deferred to future release enhanced visualization social and discovery okay sure and terraform yep
that's all all for the future okay excellent i love it i say approve um and it's a great
opportunity for us to have come in and read it and reviewed it off it goes it's now it's now
proceeding um it's creating a roadmap as the next step so it's not like you need to run the commands
that we looked at before one by one uh if you just interact with it this way then it will just drive
and it's off so much is happening you can see that the main context window is starting to fill
up this is showing how much is being used and it'll be interesting to see how it handles it
when that starts to get tight anyways again i'm going to see you in a minute i'm going to to watch
over it and i'll come back if something interesting happens okay another key moment i'm being asked
does this roadmap structure work for you here is the roadmap it suggested a proposed roadmap in 10
phases database foundation portfolio trade execution watch list app assembly llm chat
integration front-end foundation watch lists portfolio trading chat interface packaging and
testing seems very sensible to me to me it seems actually this is this is a better approach than
the the claude agents i i like the way that the ui is being deferred to a bit later that makes
sense to me i thought it was odd that claude teams began with the ui uh and and yeah the chat
interface coming near the end makes total sense to me starting with them sort of nuts and bolts
like this this this all seems really good uh let's go with a one approve let's do this okay so now
it's paused to say that next up it's now it's got the uh the project set up it's ready now i will
now have i thought maybe just launch into to phase one but it's up to me to to run the command to
kick off either to discuss phase one or to go ahead and plan phase one and you know i think
that it depends on the size and the magnitude of your project if you wanted to discuss each of the
phases i think that we should just go go right ahead and go straight into planning phase one
plan phase one let's just go straight into it and get this show on the road and so you'll notice
that phase one has now finished planning and it's ready for the uh executing and before it does that
i just want to do a slash usage and just see how much have we used now uh you can see we're now at
18 percent we've gone from uh eight percent to 18 percent so it's definitely it's quite something
that that uses up a ton of space um it's already it looks like about uh about almost double the
amount just to get to planning phase one that the entire claw teams used before so it's definitely
quite a hog on tokens and it's quite slow but this has been going for a total of an hour now
so it's a very different proposition to the team's structure that we had before um possibly i've i've
over boiled it by making it into 10 phases like this but anyway i'm gonna press ahead i'm gonna
execute this phase and then unless there's anything uh surprising that happens i'm just
going to keep on going through and see where we get to uh this is this is on yellow right now so
i'm going to also watch with interest as it deals with the context and i'll see you back when we
made some significant progress and that has now completed it's now uh it's uh completed the the
execution of phase one you can see this context looks really really uh full and we can now start
planning phase two uh we also you could i could run the the verify work but that's for a sort of
manual step which i'm not going to do so i'm going to go straight ahead uh and do a gsd uh plan
phase two uh and you can see that um that the uh the the uh context is really looking super full
i wonder i i don't know if i'm allowed to say and three like that if it can do them both together
because it says that that's also available can run in parallel with phase two let me try that
and meanwhile the context here is very full we'll see if this this command works we'll see what
happened uh it's thinking about that and uh planning phases two and three in parallel it
certainly can all right so i will let that go and i will see you in a sec well i have to confess i
have some slightly unexpected news for you the project has finished and as you'll see here it
is 100 complete the thing that maybe is the fact that i perhaps wasn't expecting i don't know if
you was is that it's actually five hours later for me than it is when i was just here with you a
second ago five hours this thing ground and ground it like thrashed over stuff it was trying to do a
couple of things in parallel a bit like the using the the agent teams but um basically it was very
serial and everything got checked and double checked in an agonizing way i have to say that
my initial reaction is it felt over storied perhaps i should have condensed some of the phases
on the roadmap earlier but for example even completing it it's taken about half an hour just
to complete the project it marked it as complete then it had to update its status to say that it
was complete and as doing so it had to rerun the tests but when it rerun the tests it hit an issue
even though the test had already run successfully and so it went back and it thrashed and it
thrashed and discovered that in fact there was some problem with the way it was running the tests
and in the end it decided uh that it was finished it says churned for one minute but that's not true
it churned for a lot longer than one minute uh so um in total if i now do slash usage and we have a
look at this uh my current session usage at 24 doesn't look too bad but that's because we've
gone past a day boundary and it reset and then used 24 this which used to be about nine percent
has jumped up to 17 and then it gone from eight to nine in the last project basically we've consumed
about 10 times the number of tokens and taken about 10 times the length of time to do it using
gsd than using the the clawed uh agent teams that we used before and so uh it was it was quite a
but it was very thorough very very disciplined going through every single step and doing tons
of documentation there's a lot of documentation a lot of code has been written an awful lot of tests
hundreds of tool calls um so so a big big thing went into this and i could have left this going
overnight and sort of woken up the next morning and it would have been working for me all through
the night so well not all through the night but for five hours of the night okay so at the end of
all of that the big question is is it going to work first time just like it worked for the other
one and is it going to look different uh so i guess we will find out uh after the break