Okay, well, here we go. We'll bring up a new terminal. We will just run scripts
slash start underscore mac dot sh. Okay, here we go. Let's give this a shot. It says it's running.
Let's go and take a look. Let's see if it's actually running. Bring this up. Here is the
browser window. Let's see what we get. Okay, it's working. It's working. The portfolio isn't empty,
but that's because it's remembered the data from the last portfolio. That's something.
Wow, that's of course because we have that database directory locally. Okay, this looks
really cool. What do you think? I think this is probably a better display. It's got a lot in
common. All right, it's amazing that it looks so similar actually. So how do we add a
ticker to this? Well, let's just buy three Apple shares. Press buy.
There we go. Three got onto the list right here, and Apple appeared right here. Okay, that's nice.
And that's the portfolio, and the cash is changing. Let's try this again. Let's go for
Meta, and let's get a 10 Meta, and press buy. I saw the cash come right the way down. Portfolios
come all the way up, and Meta is now a big part of the portfolio, but this isn't actually showing
in different colors yet. So the heat map looks a bit inferior, but generally speaking, it is
working. We'll give it that. This is pretty cool, I have to say. What just happened to Amazon? I'm
not sure, but we will come back in a sec and try out the AI assistant. Okay, so I'm going to say,
hi there. And it's thinking, hello, how can I assist you with your portfolio today? I'm going
to say, I'd like to add, let's see, what should we add? Let's add IBM to the watch list. Okay,
it's thinking. Still thinking. IBM has been added to watch list, and it has. IBM is on the watch list.
This is working. Okay, let's now say, okay, I'd like to buy one share of IBM, and sell
five shares of Meta. Let's see what happens. Let's see what happens. We're one, and we want Meta to
go down to five in our portfolio right here. It's thinking over here. We're not getting the
trademark speed from Cerebras, but there we go. It did its thing. It executed buy and sell, and I see
that IBM is up to one, and Meta is down to five. It is working, and I see our portfolio updating
down there, and that's pretty cool. So, I would say this is really nice. This chart here is
odd. I'm not sure why we're not seeing something there. It's funny that we have the same problem
in the other UI as well. It's meant to be showing Apple, I guess, and this portfolio isn't highlighting
in colors, this heat map, the way that the other one did. But otherwise, I would say this is pretty
impressive. The chat is working. This is working really nicely. That just looks terrific,
and generally speaking, it's working. I'm not sure which one I give the edge. Probably the
other one, actually. I think I give Claude Agent's team a slight one step ahead of this,
but it's pretty impressive, let's face it. I've also just dug into the code a bit to see whether
it was using our skill to call Cerebras, and I've noticed some interesting stuff here. The
code that it's got here is that it is using Cerebras, but it's not using our code. It is
using LightLLM as well, so it seems that it's read our skill, but it's taken it in a different
direction. It's using a different approach for structured outputs. This sometimes happens
when it does what we suggest and then hits some sort of a bug, and the way that it fixes the bug
is to sort of rewrite and do things differently, so I'm speculating that something like that
happened. So it still stayed true to sending it to Cerebras, but it's also doing some different
things to perhaps after encountering a bug, but generally speaking, I would say this is pretty
solid for a first implementation. Even if it did take a while, I'm pretty happy with the results,
and as a final step, we should check into GitHub. Let's just see. I know it's been taking
commits as we go, so a lot has already been committed. There's just a little bit left to
go. Some of the most recent stuff with the... Oh, that's weird that it's got a no modules,
not git ignored from the test directory. We would want to do that. That seems like a bit of a mistake,
and yeah, so I will now check this all into git so we've got it nice and tight,
and then I will see you for the wrap. Wait a second. I couldn't resist. Before we have the
wrap, I had to bring up the two user interfaces side by side, and it's kind of hard because
neither of them does well when it's squashed horizontally, but this is the first one we
built. This is the one that took half an hour and used agent teams from Claude,
and it had this slight janky problem here. It also has this problem that it can't seem to get
the prices of things that aren't on the watch list. That seems like a bug, but the UI is really
nice, and I love the way it does this, and then yeah, I think it looks very professional, and it
hasn't fallen prey to that problem where these LLMs tend to have purple backgrounds to all of
their UIs. The one that took all of the hours, the five-hour alternative, is this one. It looks very
similar. I think that it's failed on the heat map, isn't colored in in the way that the original one
was, and that this isn't quite as dramatic, but it hasn't got the same bug. It is able to deal with
new things that aren't on the watch list, and it's able to handle things better, able to add
to the watch list as we saw, and still have prices for things that get added. So from that point of
view, maybe it did a little bit better from a quality point of view, but I also really like
the original one too. So I don't know, it's your call. Of course, it's your call. Put it in the
chat in Udemy, which one you think is better. But for me, I'm going with the first one.
Actually, I think that despite the defects, which I think I could tell it to fix them
pretty quickly, and the fact that it got the whole thing done in half an hour already
speaks volumes to me. But two beautiful products. It's super fun to see them side by side,
and I hope you like that. And now, I will see you for the wrap. Well, what a day it's been. I told
you it would be a great day. I got a roller coaster. I wasn't, I have to admit, I wasn't
expecting how much I was signing up for. For you, it's just been like an hour. For me, it's been a
whole day of toiling with GSD. I understand why people love it. I see that when it's taking on
a really big project, especially if you're willing to run it in YOLO mode and just leave it be,
then it's clearly very, very diligent. I mean, honestly, when I saw it like going backwards
and forwards over confirming and double checking and triple checking that the tests were passing,
it was clearly very thorough indeed. I see why it works well. But it's a lot of time spent and a lot
of tokens spent as well. So we really saw those two sides of the spectrum. We saw the new Claude
agent teams and how it's able to be very dynamic. And then we saw the more regimented, more strict
orchestration in GSD. And I think we enjoyed two fabulous results as a result of that. And yeah,
I hope you enjoyed that. And then tomorrow we should have a fitting finale. I can't wait to
show you what I got in store for you. With that, that brings us to 93% of the way along.
We've only got 7% left and it's all tomorrow. And I can't wait to see them.