Well, hello. I can't believe it. It's the last day. It's the finale. Welcome to week three,
day five. Our last time together, at least for this journey. Well, let's make it count. I got a
great day in store for you. So yesterday was a purple day, our final purple day. We covered
the idea of having swarms of agents, lots of agents, and we had, what, seven or eight of them,
and we used Florida agent teams. And then we looked at the more robust orchestration of something
like GSD, when there's a step-by-step process and lots of checks and double checks, and it
took five hours, and we got a pretty good result. And in fact, both times, we got two zero-shot
results. And it's true, the more that I think about it, that the second one didn't have any
major defects, where the first one definitely did. Even if the first one looked, they both
looked very fancy. But it was a great result, and it really gives you that feeling of the art
of the possible, what can be achieved if you are bold. And we started out, of course, with Claude
agent teams, and I took you through this chart from Claude's website that compares sub-agents
that we're pretty familiar with now with agent teams, and how agent teams are just a bit more
out there, and the results are more unpredictable, but it's fast, and you get a lot done, and it's
really exciting. A bit nerve-wracking, but exciting. And we got great results, albeit for a reasonably
well-contained project. And then straight after this, of course, we then moved on to GSD, which
is an example of, there are many others like it, of these sort of spec-driven designs, when you
are orchestrating across lots of agents. It felt very much more serial, even though some things
happened in parallel. As I say, it took a long time, there's a lot of double-checking and
triple-checking, a lot of planning, and then executing, and then verifying. But the results do
speak for themselves. Really impressive. And in case you forgot, this is what it looked like.
This was our first result, our beautiful result, coming from Claude agent teams. And there you see
the heat map just switched. You've got this beautiful heat map, you've got this nice chat,
super fast. I just tried it. And you've got here the watch list, and the positions you've got,
and the overall portfolio P&L. Really, really nicely done. Very visual, very responsive. Look
at these. These charts are terrific. And then over here, very similar indeed, is, of course,
the result from GSD. It seems to be, as I say, more robust to new tickers being added.
And it's generally got, it does have a bit more of a polished look to it. Maybe I'm being unfair
about the purple background. After all, that is one of our brand colors in this case. They are
both, you've got to say, they're both fantastic products. Remembering, both of these cases are
zero shot. We didn't do any debugging ourselves. We didn't come back and say, this is a bug.
Both of these are just the first time we brought it up after giving it all of those instructions.
And they're huge amounts of code. And so it's just, it's extraordinary. It's absolutely
extraordinary. Well, I thought I'd bring this up one more time, the eight stages from Steve
Yaggy. And you remember, basically, stage six is what we'd already been working with for a bit.
Stage seven, we've never really done it per se. We haven't brought up 10 agents and manually
managed them, because we've allowed it to automatically manage them right away. We sort
of jumped straight to stage eight, which is the right way to do it. And we did it with agents.
And then we did it by orchestrating agents. And this chart, of course, came from a blog post by
Steve Yaggy. And the reason he did it was to introduce something that is about as radical
as you can get, which is a product that he built that's called Gastown, and that takes stage eight
to a completely different extreme. If you think that something like clawed agent teams is kind
of out there, kind of radical, compared to GSD, there's clearly very disciplined and very
structured. So if you've got GSD on one end, and you've got agent teams here, well, then Gastown
is like way over there by a mile. And we're going to take a look at it right now. Well, here I am in
the repo for Gastown, which will be linked in the resources. And I want to say one more time that
this next segment is completely optional. I recommend you watch me do it and use it as a way
to get a sense for what this is all about. If you really wish to, then for sure you can replicate
what I do. But be warned, it's a bit chaotic. It's a bit of madness. If it doesn't work out for you,
then I would just move on, take this more as a way of seeing the possible. And so let me now
walk you through the documentation for Gastown. So what is it? Well, it describes itself as a
workspace manager. But really, it's just a fancy set of kind of fabrics built around
Cloud Code or any coding agent. It even describes itself somewhere as a sort of the new IDE
construct. It's just a set of different wrappers built around coding agents, a bit like GSD.
It's trying to solve the challenge of context, of manually coordinating different agents.
You can have many agents. You can have 20 or 30 agents, according to Steve, all participating in
this. And it's basically organizing them into a hierarchy, into a structure with many different
agents taking responsibilities with things like mail between them as a way to coordinate with
all sorts of structure to try and make it be reliable and repeatable in a sort of controlled
chaos when you have 20 agents. We won't have that many on this example. We'll have maybe six to
eight, but you'll get a good sense of how it works. Now, one of the things to know about Gastown
is that it has its own lingo, a whole vocabulary of words. And you can just go with the flow and
watch what I do and sort of ignore the lingo. If you really want to dive in there, then you're
going to have to learn a few words. Take a paper and pen, write them down, get your glossary ready.
One word you'll see a lot is this thing called Beads, which is a piece of infrastructure that
was written by Steve that this is built on top of. But Beads gives it a way of having
things a bit like get issues, like lets it track different items with an ID. That's all part of
what it calls the Beads ledger that it is built on top of. And now let me tell you about the kind
of hierarchy of different agents that go to work for you. The whole of the world that you operate
in with Gastown is called your town workspace, and it sits in a directory, GT, in the top level. So
this is kind of outside the construct of like the projects folder and things like this. This has its
own folder in its own right. GT in your home directory, that is your town workspace. And each
of your projects are called rigs. So that is the first of the big words you have to remember.
A project is known as a rig in the Gastown terminology. So there are rigs. We're going
to have a rig called Fin for the Finally project. And you'll also see at some point that I have an
old rig called Finally because I started with that and it broke. And so there's like an old
one hanging out there. So you'll see I have two rigs, but Fin is going to be the main rig that I
will work with. That is a project. Okay, only two more words to know. Crew. Crew is like a workspace
that you will have in your project. You'll see that mine will be called Ed. So Ed will be a crew
working in Fin. And so you have a crew in your rig. Crew in the rig. Crew is Ed, rig is Fin.
And then the other thing is called a Polcat. And a Polcat is a worker. So we will end up having
many Polcats. Each Polcat gets assigned tasks and it works on them. So you're going to see a bunch
of these Polcats. All right. So Polcat is like a worker, a worker agent. A crew is like Ed's crew.
And a rig is the project. And then there's one more thing to mention, which is called the Mayor.
And the Mayor, as far as you're concerned, feels like a Claude Code. When you launch the Mayor,
up comes Claude Code. In fact, all of these are all Claude Codes as well. There's tons of
Claude Codes running, but you don't directly interact with them. You interact with one
Claude Code, and that is the Mayor. That is the Claude Code that you and I will talk to.
We will first interact with that one. And there is a way for us to flip and see all the other
Claude Codes running behind the scenes. So that is called the Mayor. The Mayor is the coordinator,
the one you talk to. And then these different things talk to each other through a mailbox.
There's tons of stuff. And I'm scraping the surface of all the action that happens when you
use this. It feels like tons is going on. And my full understanding is fairly surface level,
as you can tell. But you'll see that it will all hold together. We're going to have a Mayor. We're
going to have a rig. We're going to have a crew. We're going to have Polcats. And together, they're
going to work on Finn. But you shouldn't take my word for it. You should read all of this. You
can read the definitions of the town, the rigs, the crew members, the Polcats. And then I should
also say a convoy. I can't believe I forgot that. A convoy is like a bundle of tasks. The tasks each
are different beads. A bundle of tasks that get assigned to one of the agents, one of the Polcats.
And you'll see convoys being created and beads being created. And you can do all of that by
just talking with the Mayor. You don't need to. There are various commands to create all of these
things. But you can also just put it in natural language to the Mayor. And they will do it for you.
And yeah, it explains how tasks have this ID that they are assigned. All right. And then to install
it, to install it on a Mac, it's this simple command brew install Gastown on a PC. It's this
one. When I ran this and it installed beads as well and installed everything, everything got set
up. I just ran it in a terminal. So you should just bring up a terminal on a PC, a PowerShell.
And then run it there. If you're on a PC, it'd be better to do it in WSL and run Tmux.
If you know what that is, it's going to make the experience better. And if you don't know what any
of that is, remember, you don't need to do this. You can just watch me. I'm going to probably say
that a ton of times. You can watch me do it and just get a sense of it. This is to show you this
sort of radical semi-chaos of running a big orchestration platform together. All right.
Let's go to a terminal and get the show on the road. Okay. I've actually brought up a terminal.
What you're looking at here is a terminal. If you're on a Mac, this is the terminal program.
I'm actually using something called iTerm2. If you're on a PC, then PowerShell. And follow the
instructions that are in the GitHub repo that I'll link. And don't feel like you have to do this. You
could just watch me because I just want to give you a feel for what this is like. And the command
start GT for Gastown. I'm going to start by installing it in my home directory in a folder
called GT. And telling it to use Git. And that is the normal way that it's set up. And it's done.
And it has been created. And I'm now going to go into that directory. That's where I am right now.
And now I'm going to create a rig. So, I do GT, not Git. GT rig add. And I name the rig. And I
will call it Fin. And it's a bit like finally. But it's Fin. Like the very end. And I've got a
repo. The next thing you do is you give it a GitHub repo. It's at GitHub.com. And it's just called
Fin for the end. There we go. Done. All setting up happened. Okay. And it has all been set up.
And now the next thing to do is to add a crew to this rig. So, rig and crew are the two big
concepts. And I do that with GT crew add. I give it a name. I'll call it Ed. I tell it the rig
dash dash rig. And the name of the rig is Fin. So, that has now set up a crew called Ed for Fin.
And now I can go into that directory. So, that is in it is in the rig's directory. So,
there should now be a directory called Fin. It says just above. Start working with it.
Go into Fin slash crew slash Ed. And that is where I now am. And there is this is now where
my repo has been cloned. There is a single file called spec. And now with all of this,
I can type this command, GT mayor attach. And this is going to launch Claude Code and go into
it. Let's see that happening. It launches Claude Code. Here it is. Claude Code is running. And
it's looking at what's going on. It's looking for instructions. And it says no hooked work,
no mail, inbox is empty, waiting for instructions. And now, now I can give it instructions. Now,
there's many ways to do it. And we're going to try and do it the simplest way.