Well, I was wrong to be too confident.
When I went to the website, after asking it to bring it up,
I got a page cannot be displayed.
I got a total fail.
Nothing was there.
So I went back to the mayor,
and I said to the mayor, there's nothing there.
I didn't try and debug it, didn't diagnose it myself.
I just said, please just go ahead and fix it.
Sling your tasks, get the poll cats involved.
Let's make this happen.
And bam, it did it all over again.
Lots of things happened.
All of these six poll cats, eight poll cats all started up.
Things happened.
And now we're coming back for the second time.
And I'll mention again that we should give it some credit
because it's really starting from absolute nothing.
The other times we've had a build
using the market data foundation
and the extra documentation for market data.
This time it just started from the spec, the plan.md.
And that was it.
So it's a total build from absolute scratch.
That's what it had to do.
And it did it all massively parallel.
So it's very fast,
by far the fastest of any of the things that I've done.
And a couple of other things to mention
in the terminology, you saw me struggling there a bit,
but I do now remember.
The thing called refinery that was running
was a special agent, a special worker
that is responsible for doing the merge requests, the MRs.
And that's merging in the work
that all the others are doing.
So the reason that that was idle for a long time
is because there were no MRs for it to merge.
And then it would suddenly pick up an MR
when one of the poll cats was done.
And that's why you'd see it kick into gear.
And the reason that there was a red refinery there
was because of that other project I told you about
that I'd run before called Finally.
So it had its own refinery that was kind of dead.
And that's what was going on.
And the process called Witness
is the thing responsible for watching all of this
and notifying, I think it notifies the mayor
if anything were to go wrong.
So that's how it all hung together.
And now, without further ado,
let's see if we have a product.
All right, here we go.
I told it to bring it up on port 8002.
Here we go, we do have a product.
We do have a product.
And it looks remarkably similar to our other products,
which at the end of the day is not super surprising
because we specced things out quite carefully
in that planning document.
And it was fairly precise.
And also, after all, it's always Claude Code.
It's always Opus 4.6 that's building all of these.
But it's interesting
that we end up with very similar results.
So here we have something we've got over here on the left.
And it's interesting,
this time it says select a ticker from the watch list.
And maybe that's what I was meant to do in the other one.
But if I think if I click here, yeah, look at that.
Then we get to see the one that I just clicked on
appearing here in this chart.
And what happens now if I click here
and I say Apple quantity three, and I click buy,
then bang, Apple appears in the portfolio heat map
over on the right.
And I can also do Netflix.
And we will buy for Netflix, press buy.
And the heat map is updated over here.
The portfolio, we've got positions here.
It's super impressive.
Particularly again, I mean,
we can't really call it a zero shot this time
because it took an iteration, didn't it?
So it took two iterations,
but I didn't give it any particular feedback.
I didn't help it troubleshoot.
It figured all this out for itself.
And this whole thing is running and it's alive.
Wow, it's time to try the LLM part.
All right, so over here, I click in the chat.
I'm gonna say hi there and let's see what happens.
Takes a bit of time.
Hello, how can I help with your portfolio today?
I'm going to say, please buy three shares of JPM.
Let's see what happens.
Drum roll, please.
Sure, I will place an order.
Bam, look at that.
JP Morgan appears here, nice and green.
I like to see that.
And it's all updating everywhere.
The AI chat works.
That's absolutely amazing. This is great.
This you see right here is the result of running Gastown,
building our entire project,
including the market data simulator
and the market data interface.
The whole thing built from scratch and running and working.
And so to recap, if I haven't completely confused you,
we've been talking about using orchestrators or patterns
for allowing us to manage multiple agents working together,
but with some level of coordination between them
to allow for more predictable outcomes.
And we've really looked at three of them
and we could put them alongside each other
in a line from the most kind of controlled and disciplined
through to the most crazy.
The GSD, the Get Done,
is perhaps despite the radical sounding name,
the one that is most disciplined.
It is from the family of spec driven designs.
When there is a clear spec,
it uses markdown files very cautiously.
It goes through a period of plan, of reviewing,
of execution, and then validating,
and then an audit at the end of it.
So it's this very reliable discipline process,
which lends itself to bigger projects,
to human in the loop,
and to being able to deliver measurable,
predictable outcomes.
Okay, so it's more reliable, it's more slow.
Then in the middle, we met Claude Agent Teams.
And it's the experimental feature.
Maybe it's now more mature for you.
And it's for sure, it is faster.
It took five hours with GSD.
It took about half an hour with Claude Agent Teams.
And then we ended on Gastown.
I just gave you a preview of it.
I told you, you don't need to do this yourself
unless you particularly want to go through the experience
that I went through,
when I seemed a bit frazzled in places.
But of course, this kind of thing is emerging now.
There are a few like it.
Gastown is the one that's quite hyped at the moment,
but there might be many, many more.
And these are ones where there is a sort of
preset structure, but it's ready
for a lot of concurrent work.
It took about the same time as Claude Agent Teams,
I think, in total, about half an hour.
But it did a lot more,
because we gave it the market data task as well.
It built the whole thing from scratch,
and it just all worked.
Second time, but just with me telling it,
hey, go and fix this.
And so that was the most chaotic.
It was the fastest in terms of building the most
in the same amount of time.
And it was pretty impressive,
if a little bit bewildering.
And now GSD is something which can be applied to,
I think, all of the coding agents.
And Gastown is also something which Steve points out a lot
in the blog post or in the GitHub readme,
something that can be applied
to the different coding agents.
It's not tied to Claude Code,
even though he first built it around it.
Claude Agent Teams, of course,
is a feature built into Claude Code.
But as it happens, there are some very similar feature,
similar agent features are built into the others.
And in particular, I took a look at Codex,
and Codex has something that's also experimental,
built into Codex.
And I wouldn't be doing my job
if I didn't quickly give you a sneak peek of that.
No surprise, I'm sure you're getting the idea
that I most favor the ones in the middle.
I like Claude Agent Teams a lot.
Between these, it was the one that gave me
the experience of a lot of power
without feeling like I was completely out of control.
But I'm sure that if you spend enough time with Gastown,
you get really used to it.
Anyway, let's go check out Codex Subagents.
So I'm not actually gonna run it,
because I already run it,
and I think you've seen enough of these now.
I'm just gonna sort of show you the Codex
and show you how you activate the feature
and then show you the results.
But I'm back in a normal terminal window
and I wanna remind you of sprites. Remember this?
I can say sprite, sorry, sprite.dev is the full name of it.
I can do sprite list to see all of the sprites
which I've got running,
all of these remote sandboxed environments
that fly.io is running for me.
And I've got one called finally worker, the same one.
And you can do sprite, sprint,
sprite minus S, finally worker,
that's how you say which one you're talking about,
and then console.
And that means I wanna like remote in,
I want this terminal to become a terminal for that sprite.
And that's what we're looking at right now. So if I do,
unless I can see there's a directory called finally in there,
I can go into finally, now I'm in finally.
And this is in particular, if I do get status,
this repo is got, it's on branch Codex.
I created this branch called Codex.
And when running Codex inside your sprite,
you just type Codex, it's already installed,
but you do minus minus YOLO.
That is the equivalent
of dangerously skip permissions for Claude.
They've got a couple of them for Codex,
but dash dash YOLO is one way to do it.
And we're now in Codex, in YOLO mode.
And in Codex, you can do slash
to bring up a slash command menu,
just as the Claude code.
And I went to slash experimental,
which is where you get to toggle on and off
experimental features.
And the one I picked is called sub agents,
and I asked Codex to spawn multiple agents
to parallelize the work and to win in efficiency.
And so of course I selected that.
And then I just said,
hey, check out plan.md and do this.
That's what I did.
It's not the only thing I did,
because if I come out of here,
if I just do an LS,
you'll also notice that I renamed Claude.md
to agents.md, because I remembered
that Codex expects agents.md not Claude.md.
So that made it work.
And I think I also told it,
let's have a look in scripts,
cat start underscore Mac.
We can see what we've got right here.
Yeah, I wanted it to come up on port 8003.
That's how it should run.
And so, and I believe that is now running.
Let's do a Docker PS to see if it's running.
And this should tell us whether or not
Docker is installed and is running.
And the idea is we expect it to be running.
It's not running, so I will start it.
I'll do scripts slash start.
And this is a Linux box,
but Mac scripts is the same.
And now it should be coming up and running. There we go.
And it is now running on port 8003.
So that is built and running.
It was built in parallel.
And I got to tell you, it was super fast.
It was faster than any of them.
I don't know if it just happened
to be having a good day,
but it was really very quick.
It took, I'd say maybe 15 minutes end to end.
So it was the fastest as these experiments go of any of them.
And we will see if we can, whatever,
zero shot it, see how it is,
if we try and bring it up.
And of course it's running in my Sprite on port 8003.
And what I want to do is see what's happening
on my, I want to be able to bring it up
on my computer on port 8003.
How's that going to work?
I need to like connect it to the Sprite
out there in the internet.
But luckily there's a beautiful command I can do,
which is Sprite minus S,
finally worker, finally dash worker.
There's a command that is called proxy, proxy.
And then you do the name of the port
and that is going to take port 8003
on finally worker and map it to my local port.
So I can just bring up a browser,
point it to 8003 and see what's going on on that.
Okay, let's try it.