Okay it's time to see what Codex did in 15 minutes when equipped with the same prompt as the others
but first let's do a quick recap shall we not let me begin by showing you again the GSD not the
first one we did it was it was the second one we did I think but GSD which was the most thorough
five hours five hours in the making this was what we got this quite professional looking one a bit
less flashy than some of the others let's just do a quick buy three apple let's see what happens
there it appears now that I understand this funny thing that confused me about this chart I guess we
should try clicking here now that doesn't make any difference I was wondering if that was going
to make it appear on the chart here uh oh look it changes the title up there so maybe it is working
we just have to leave it a bit perhaps maybe that's how that's meant to work uh and uh let's
just try here buy three shares of goog and make sure that that works uh and it's thinking hopefully
that's going to work yeah executed it's got a very nice looking thing there and there's some google
okay that was number one and now I want to show you the claude agents one check this one out
it looks really nice uh I like the way that all of this flashes like this and if I click there
yeah okay so I guess I just didn't get this the first time I saw the user interface because
you click here and this updates and I think you have to wait a while for this chart to start
appearing uh but I totally didn't didn't realize that um and uh we can say um here please uh
purchase one share of jpm see what happens there there we go it's bought one jp morgan
there we have it very nice uh okay so this this one here is the claude agents one my favorite one
to work with I like the user interface as well I'm not sure what you think looks very nice now
we'll switch to the next one which is the gas town one we just saw this they all look quite
similar uh and this is the interaction that we already just had just to flip through them again
uh this is I'm getting confused but this is gsd claude agents and then this one is gas town those
are the three it's hard to keep it together they look very similar and of course not a big surprise
it was opus 4.6 building them all just orchestrated differently and with the first one taking five
hours that maybe it overworked it um okay and now I'm going to show you kodak's uh different
orchestration and a different look here we have it wow it does look different I mean it has a lot
of similarities it has the same kind of uh the same kind of uh cut black look and the same flashing
thing over here but I gotta tell you I I think this is really nice it might be because sometimes
a change just looks better you know but I think this looks great I love the the effect of these
here they look really professional really sleek this user interface just looks very very nice
uh and uh so I love it it's very similar but this chart is clearly improved uh and yeah now when I
flick through I see I see it changing very nice indeed uh really impressive I love it and let's
ask it to do a trade let's uh buy one share of meta let's see what happens order place to buy
one share of meta and there's meta and uh it's happening so it's very nice I like the way the
portfolio up there uh updates so so fast are they all doing that yes they are of course they are oh
but not this one check that out that looks like a small bug that we have there with my my favorite
one lord agents maybe not so good after all and is this one updating no nor is gsd so the only
ones that were able to keep the portfolio oh no look there the portfolio's gone static uh so it
looks like this this is something that that openai's codex won on that front it has something
really nice there so some great implementations to my surprise I've got to tell you that actually
the codex implementation codex 5.3 this is uh is perhaps my personal winner a late breaking surprise
and this is the the only one that didn't um the the that didn't use uh the uh we didn't have the
skill so we didn't give it the extra skill to know how to use cerebras although it seems to
figure everything out um and it's uh yeah the one that just took 15 minutes it was the fastest to
build and it came up with perhaps perhaps in my opinion the best outcome but you should tell me
what you think your best outcome is uh please put your notes uh in the in the chat let me know what
you think um and hopefully you're experimenting with this yourself and here I have to show you
one more time the final results this is the codex version but you'll see something's different here
you'll see first of all everything looks quite green and secondly you'll see that there's not
much going on it doesn't appear to be flashing just every so often and there's a few reasons
for that one of them is that I have just switched to using the true polygon now massive market data
so that this is actually showing real live market data this is the real stock price of JP Morgan
right now the reason it's all a bit green is that this is after hours at the moment it is just past
trading cut off so there's not much happening there's some after hours activity which is why
there are occasional changes if we were during the middle of the trading day you would see more
action but it's pretty cool that you're looking at real stock prices here this is now the actual
platform that is showing a true market data simulator with the real results coming through
and it wasn't just a matter of changing the the putting in the polygon the massive key because it
didn't work first time because the code that Claude wrote didn't actually work immediately it
had a wrong hard-coded key in there and I told codex codex found the problem fixed it and then
codex told me hey you realize it's after trading hours so it's going to be a bit static there'll
be a bit of after hours movement and of course codex was exactly right and so in conclusion what
you're looking at really is a kind of modern day simulated trading environment a modern
Bloomberg-esque terminal with a position heat map with an AI chat with real live market data that's
just flashing occasionally as after hours trading activity occurs and it's pretty impressive all in
all all of these solutions are pretty impressive but for me as it happens whilst as you can probably
tell Claude Code is my favorite platform I love the tooling I will say that on this occasion at
least I believe that codex emerges as the leader of the pack but wait there's more there's always
one more thing and here is the one more thing let's let's I'm back in a terminal again let's go
sprite list to see our list of sprites that we've got running we've just got the one called
finally worker and I do sprite minus s finally worker console to re-attach to that sprite
running in the cloud there we are we are now running uh we are using ssh we are we are
remoted in to the sprite running in the cloud and I've mentioned a few times something called
which is something that you can run on Linux and Mac systems that lets you take a terminal and break
it into multiple terminals I'll put the commands and the resources I've set up a tmux so that there
are four consoles running and I can reattach to them at any point and I've called it quad because
it divides things into quads and now I can type tmux attach minus t quad to reattach to my four
terminals that have been running and here they are bam four terminals for you so what do I have
here I have four different terminals I can flip between them in tmux by doing ctrl b and then
right to go to the right hand one ctrl b and down arrow keys to go to the bottom right ctrl b and
left to go over there ctrl b up and I'm back up at the top left again it's very similar to the
ctrl b uh up and down that we did when we were moving between tmux sessions before and I've got
four different terminal windows the one on the top left is running codex codex in yolo mode the
one on the top right is running claude in dangerously skip permissions mode which is it's
yolo mode bottom left is another codex I've got two codexes running and the bottom right I'm using
for my git workflow to check things in but even is so this is like three different coding agents
running but within that the codex on the top left is running codex with sub-agents activated so it
can use agents to run multiple things and as well you know claude is able to use claude agent teams
so that claude can run a bunch of agents or of course it can also use sub-agents so we've got
this kind of ability to have three different kind of heads that we're talking to that can have
themselves gangs of agents and I have just been riffing with this for the last couple of hours
and I've mostly been doing market data work and and back-end work with codex on the top left and
ui stuff with claude on the top right and I've been tracking stuff in markdown files using that
best practice I've been keeping things together and they've been making great progress together
as a team and it's been quite hard work managing everything going on but I've always been the boss
I've just been telling them what to do I've not dug into the code I've just asked them to look
at things and occasionally review each other's stuff too so powerful and we've made tons of
progress and it's one more time for me to mention to you this thing this this frame of mind you have
to be in that you can often make make tons of progress in a short amount of time you feel like
you are on fire you've you're 10xing your performance you really are and then you hit
like a like a block a roadblock of some sort a bug and and the agents just keep hitting the same
problem and can't get their way through it and you find that you spend a lot of time just getting over
a small obstacle and you can feel like ah I'm wasting all of my time it's it's uh it's not this
10x but you have to keep in mind still even when you factor that in the amount of time that it's
taken me to make lots of progress a couple of hours is still multiple times two or three times
faster than if I was writing all this myself so never never be surprised when that initial 10x
then gets pulled back by some bugs keep in mind it's still a significant net positive so that is
my important message to you to keep keep fuel in the tank to be ready to hit problems and expect
to spend a lot of your time a large portion of your time carefully reproducing get down the issue
let's understand the issue before we fix it make a markdown file explaining the issue
and now fix it and now test and prove you fixed it that process and even then discovering the
problem's still there no you didn't fix it that can take time be ready for that expect it it is
part of the new way okay that's enough preamble it's time for me to reveal to you the fruits of
the labor not of me but of these coding agents this is the result of a few coding agents each
with multiple sub agents a few hours of work let's see it here i present to you the finally or fin
ally trader workstation with live market data courtesy of massive you are looking at a watch
list of 60 stock tickers divided into tech financials health care consumer industrials
and energy they are being live updated as the markets change you are looking at the live ticker
of apple on the display there you are looking at the portfolio pnl and our heat map and the llm chat
this this is our trader workstation let's agree this is sensational and it will come as no surprise
to you to see that now i can click on one of these tickers and zoom in on it and see on the right the
main chart of what's going on there is netflix is it appears to be having a bit of a journey
downwards there uh so you see everything that is happening on this dashboard absolutely amazing
and there's one more little trick to show you claude added this little feature uh which i will
show you now which is this symbol up here in case you are somewhat tired of these slight gamer style
dark mode ui's you can flip it to light mode check that out it just looks so fresh and
professional and clean it's like wow and flip it back to dark mode again if if that's your preferred
style light mode and dark mode done just like that i am floored by this it is just fantastic
i kid you not if you'd shown me this a couple of years ago and asked me how long it would take to
build this i don't know what you'd said i probably said this would take me a month or two i would
have charged a fair amount of money for this uh even even though it's i'd still argue it's probably
still a demo app uh in the there aren't there isn't the user login side of it yet and you can't
deploy it yet uh those are pretty easy steps now because it's all in a docker container those are
just small steps to take this into a proper commercial app so i would probably say this
is a month or two worth of work for me and and it would have been a really hard project and it was
just super easy it honestly was and hopefully you've got the same kinds of results hopefully
you're building that look towards building something like this i'll put in the course
resources how you could get of course exactly this code base and see it for yourself but it's
much more fun to build it yourself or do something different do something that takes it in a different
direction that you like but with a similar wow factor that this has and then by all means
add to your agent that it should deploy it deploying a container is relatively easy
they'll walk you through the instructions and help you make any decisions you need to make
about which which vendor you use and then you can have this live on the internet too
just a brilliant project and and just a great capstone finale moment for us