But wait, there's more.
There's one more thing.
I just had a 15-minute conversation,
I kid you not, with Codex.
We talked about the best place to deploy this on the Internet,
and we agreed that using Fly.io,
the company behind Sprites.dev,
would be a great choice for deploying a container as is.
It wrote a script for me,
we ran the script,
we've deployed, and you're looking here,
if you just look at the URL up there,
you are looking at finally-ed.fly.dev.
This is deployed live on the Internet.
The AI chat works,
the portfolio is there,
the market data is live,
we set up the environment variables correctly,
everything is running,
this is now deployed,
and deployment took all of 15 minutes,
and you should do it too.
So here, finally,
I leave you finally with the project, finally,
deployed on the Internet with live market data,
and a nice light look to boot.
And so take a last look at the different orchestrators
that we've used.
I would say that my favorite experience
is with Cloud Agent Teams,
and the winner of the prize in this case was probably Codex.
It did a fine job there,
and of course I used it through Sprite.dev,
which is such a powerful way to use these agents,
because you can use a coding agent in YOLO mode
and feel completely secure, which is great.
So the big challenge for you now
is to take the repo as it stands
and give one of these things a try.
If you're using a free model,
maybe you're using open code with a free model
or an open source cheap model,
then you may have a more challenging experience
maybe using something as disciplined as GSD
is your way of getting there.
If you are splashing out
and using something like local code,
then you should have an easy old time with it,
but see if you can't challenge it
to do something a bit different.
Maybe you want to add in a kind of the users table
so different people can log in
as we had it in week two in the SaaS legal platform,
add in that functionality as well.
So take it in your direction.
Remember, the amazing thing about these coding agents
is that it's a choose your own adventure story.
You've got a really robust specification there
in the form of the cloud.md,
and now you can build something
and take it somewhere new,
give yourself your own trader workstation and enjoy it
and see whether you get similar outcomes to me
and whether you find that Claude or Codex
or some other model is the winner.
And let me know, share your results,
please on Udemy, tell me what you discover
or of course share it on LinkedIn.
That's a great place to share it.
Put it on LinkedIn, show what you've got.
And I will weigh in,
I will add some comments if you tag me
and I will make sure that I amplify your success.
And again, if you see other students doing this,
then please jump in yourself
and add some comments to theirs as well.
That really helps amplify the whole community
if we're there to support each other.
Okay, it's time for a wrap up.
It's time for us to go to the final segment.
Stay for the final segment
because it's always good to wrap things up.
But unfortunately, this is the tearful moment
when we finish things off
and what better place to finish things off
than going back again to the Andrej Karpathy tweet
that started this whole course.
And I'm going to read it to you one more time.
But this time, it's like I'm speaking to you
in a foreign language at the beginning
and then at the end,
once you've learned all of the vocabulary,
hopefully it all will fall into place. Andrej says,
I've never felt this much behind as a programmer.
Profession is being refactored
as the bits contributed by a programmer are becoming sparse.
I could be 10 times more powerful
if I could just string together
everything that's become available.
There's a new layer of abstraction to master
with agents, sub-agents,
their prompts, context, memory, modes,
permissions, tools, plugins, skills,
hooks, MCP, LSP, slash commands,
workflows, IDEs,
and the need to build an all-encompassing mental model
for the strengths and pitfalls
of fundamentally stochastic, fallible,
unintelligible, and changing entities.
Clearly, a powerful alien tool was handed around
except it comes with no manual
and everyone has to figure out how to operate it
while the resulting magnitude nine earthquake
is rocking the profession.
Roll up your sleeves to not fall behind.
So obviously, the bad news is
that it's not like I've given you
total transparency and clarity
because this world is moving so fast.
And when we look at things like Gastown,
it still feels completely bewildering for me,
let alone for you.
So yes, it is a bit crazy out there,
but I do hope, at least now,
that you've dimensioned the landscape.
You've got a good sense of things like plugins and skills
and when to use each,
and you've got that hands-on experience
working, first of all, in the IDEs,
but then, of course, in the CLIs
with Cloud Code or Codex.
And now you know about things
that Andre didn't even mention,
like sandboxing that's so important and powerful
and how you can use that with YOLO mode
and you know about Ralph Loops.
And now you also know about GSD.
You know about all these different bits and pieces
and you've experimented with them.
And that's perhaps the most important thing
that I have to say to you.
The single most important thing
is you need to be willing to experiment.
There's not necessarily one right answer.
The great thing about using these coding agents
is you can kick it off,
let it build something.
If it all goes wrong,
just simply start again.
Try it again with a different approach.
As you think about the approaches,
keep this chart in mind.
I know I've gone through this like 100 times,
but typically for more mission-critical stuff,
large code bases,
for code that is at the forefront,
so it may not be in much
of the coding agent's training data,
keep to the top row, the yellow.
Look at managing with lots of markdown files,
taking things very incrementally,
and the top right, SDD, spec-driven design.
That's things like GSD.
It's worlds where you work step-by-step
through a clear workflow,
that kind of approach.
And a trust but verify mindset.
And if you're doing MVPs, new build,
you've got some risk appetite,
you're churning out boilerplate code,
go for the purples.
YOLO, but in a sandbox,
in something like sprite.dev,
or in like a managed Claude on the web.
YOLO, use Ralph Loops perhaps,
and then the whole idea of multi-agent swarms
and orchestration that we've been doing
the last couple of days.
And to give you some of the big takeaways,
you should pick the right coding agent
and the workflow to use
based on how mature the project is
and what sort of risk appetites you have.
Your personal skills,
what's going to suit,
if you're a seasoned pro,
then you're probably leaning towards the CLI tools.
If you're still getting used to this,
then maybe the IDEs are gonna feel
more comfortable for you.
And just your preference,
like the mode of work that you enjoy.
Some people just love working in CLIs,
and some people just prefer
having the interactivity of an IDE,
and you also potentially get familiar
with some of the models.
You might just like Claude.
It might just work for you.
It works for me.
And then follow these steps.
First thing to look at is the plugins.
Plugins, it's easy to look at the official plugins
and pick the most popular ones
or the ones that, out of the most popular ones
that were gonna work for your project,
like FeatureDev,
or the one that simplifies code,
or that builds professional front ends.
Pick the plugins that are gonna work for you.
And then next up, typically skills
is the next thing to do.
Picking skills are gonna really work nicely
for your project.
And this is also an opportunity to use an MCP server
if there are MCP servers like Contact 7,
which is exactly what you need.
Although there's also the plugin for that too.
And then just be willing to do trial and error.
Just have that experimenter's mindset.
Kick it off, see what happens.
If it's not gonna work for you,
you can just throw it away and go back
and having that mindset is just so critical.
And obviously make heavy use of Git.
It is your friend.
It gives you such an easy ability
to go back to where you were
and also be disciplined about markdown docs.
Get things to write to markdown.
Use that as it sort of baked into some of these workflows.
Use it as your way of tracking what's going on
just as we've been doing both in weeks two and three.
That is such a great process.
And on that note,
also just generally manage your context.
In Cloud Code, do slash context all the time.
See what's going on.
Don't wait for your context to compact.
Manage it yourself.
Write stuff out to markdown.
Write stuff to cloud.md or agents.md
and then do a slash clear to start again
and be fresh with your context.
Being proactive about context management
is just the right way to do it.
And finally, remember you own the quality
of the code that you push.
Remember that AI PR policy from Jellyfin?
Keep that in mind.
This is code that you stand behind.
Don't let your coding agent build slop.
Don't let it put tons of extra test files or readmes
and please no emojis.
Be ruthlessly on top of it.
Make things sharp and good quality code. Own the code.
Make sure that it is good quality.
Okay, those are the major takeaways.