And with that, and with that, we've reached the last few minutes of this program.
You remember, we started out in week one, Vibe coding for fun and profit.
We built out, we went through all of the IDEs, just introducing like
agents.md, Cursor, Copilot, Codex, Antigravity, looking at all those
plugins and the IDEs themselves.
Then our first experience with YOLO, it feels like an age away.
And then the commercial MVP that was cool.
Then we moved into Claw Code and OpenCode and AMP.
It was commands and checkpoints for the first time, slash commands and Ralph loops.
And then we, we, things got more serious.
We, we got to see that whole workflow with Jira. That was cool.
All the way going through to, to a Git push and built out that legal SaaS platform.
And that finally took us to week three.
By this point, I said that you are now Vibe engineering.
You've gone from Vibe coding to Vibe engineering as a professional.
And now this week was so much fun.
I knew it would be.
We just went crazy with, first of all, the idea of multi-agents, which is kind of
worrying, but then sub-agents, I showed you hooks, sandboxing was a much more
interesting day than it might've sounded just from the name, sandboxing, when we
were doing, I think that for me anyway, Sprite.dev is the, is the really, really
great thing, but also running with, with Claw Code remotely, hopefully you tried
the, the ampersand thing and also using it from your mobile and then also tagging
Claw in a Git issue. It's fantastic.
And then the large code-based workflow day, I didn't really do much about what
large code-based workflow, because I felt like we covered it enough.
But yeah, instead we, we spent a moment looking at some of the other stuff. I got it.
I think that, that Claw Agent SDK is really interesting.
Something that's definitely worth more exploration.
If, if you found that, that's something useful.
And then of course we looked at co-work and OpenClaw was just
something to take a nod at.
It's a, it's all over the news, at least for me at the moment.
And then the last couple of days have just been so great.
Looking at orchestrators, of course, GSD, Clawed Agent Teams, which,
which is definitely my favorite.
And then also the, the craziness that is Gastown, which was something we did
today and then we finally, very quickly, I showed you Codex sub-agents and then
getting Codex to fix up the massive API.
So we could have a real finance workstation.
Hopefully you've recreated that yourself.
That completed our capstone project, project number four.
But I know what you're thinking.
It's, we didn't do four projects.
We did six projects because we also did the first person shooter on the first
day and we did the space invaders.
So they count as projects.
So that would make it six projects, four commercial projects though.
And that means of course, that you are no longer a vibe coder.
You are no longer a vibe engineer.
You are now an officially an agentic engineer.
I can fill in that third strip.
You have completed the board. It's done.
You're an agentic engineer.
Congratulations.
And it remains for me to give you a huge thank you.
Thank you so much for surviving the rollercoaster, making it all the way to the end.
I promised you a rollercoaster and I think I delivered.
So remember, whether you like it or not, something came with this package that is
that is yours that you can't avoid.
It's like, like a mandatory part of it. And that is me. I come with it.
You, you, you, you get me forever.
I want you to, to, to reach out to me, post on LinkedIn that you've completed the
course with something you've learned, some insight, something about it.
And, and I will come in and amplify your success.
Make sure that others know about it.
I'd love it if you post some of the projects you've built or some of your
thoughts on, on what you like and dislike about the different platforms
we've covered or the techniques.
Uh, as I say, post the certificate.
That's something that is easy for me to amplify.
I would love to do so.
Take a look through some of my other courses.
If that interests you.
Uh, I've got lots of stuff to build you into being an AI engineer.
I have a program for people who want to become proficient AI engineers.
I should also mention my editor would kill me if I didn't mention again,
that, that, uh, to the extent that you're willing to rate this course,
that is the main way that Udemy decides whether or not to recommend it to others.
So if you found it useful, then please do rate it.
It makes an enormous difference and I'm super grateful, but more
important than any of this, the single most important thing for you
that to do that you must do is to build.
It's all about building.
I hope that I have equipped you with the missing manual to this,
this alien tool that Andhra Karpathy spoke of.
You now have the ability to use this tool.
Go use it, go build some amazing things, build them, share them with me.
I can't wait to see them.
Thank you so much again.